* 

* How We Can Help
    
    * [###### Programs For You
        
        A healthier you is within reach. Omada is a virtual care program that helps you achieve your health goals.
        
        Learn More](https://www.omadahealth.com/for-individuals)
        
        * [
            
            Prevention](https://www.omadahealth.com/for-individuals/prediabetes)
        * [
            
            Diabetes](https://www.omadahealth.com/for-individuals/diabetes)
        * [
            
            Hypertension](https://www.omadahealth.com/for-individuals/hypertension)
        * [
            
            Joint & Muscle Health](https://www.omadahealth.com/for-individuals/musculoskeletal)

    * [###### Member Support
        
        Whatever you need, the Omada team is here to help.
        
        Learn More](https://support.omadahealth.com/hc/en-us)
        
        * [
            
            Help Center](https://support.omadahealth.com/hc/en-us)
        * [
            
            Member Blog](https://resourcecenter.omadahealth.com/for-individuals)
        * [
            
            Contact Us](https://www.omadahealth.com/contact)
        * [
            
            Privacy Policy](https://www.omadahealth.com/privacy-policy)

* Search

Health programs built just for you. Check your eligibility today!

* * *

[For Organizations 

Quality virtual care that is personal, connected, & sustainable.](#)[Contact Sales ](https://www.omadahealth.com/contact-sales)   

* How We Can Help
    
    * [###### Programs For You
        
        A healthier you is within reach. Omada is a virtual care program that helps you achieve your health goals.
        
        Learn More](https://www.omadahealth.com/for-individuals)
        
        * [
            
            Prevention](https://www.omadahealth.com/for-individuals/prediabetes)
        * [
            
            Diabetes](https://www.omadahealth.com/for-individuals/diabetes)
        * [
            
            Hypertension](https://www.omadahealth.com/for-individuals/hypertension)
        * [
            
            Joint & Muscle Health](https://www.omadahealth.com/for-individuals/musculoskeletal)

    * [###### Member Support
        
        Whatever you need, the Omada team is here to help.
        
        Learn More](https://support.omadahealth.com/hc/en-us)
        
        * [
            
            Help Center](https://support.omadahealth.com/hc/en-us)
        * [
            
            Member Blog](https://resourcecenter.omadahealth.com/for-individuals)
        * [
            
            Contact Us](https://www.omadahealth.com/contact)
        * [
            
            Privacy Policy](https://www.omadahealth.com/privacy-policy)

* Search

    * [###### Who We Serve
        
        Omada's integrated care pathways deliver lasting change, meaningful outcomes, and cost savings to our partners.
        
        Learn More](https://www.omadahealth.com/for-organizations)[](https://www.omadahealth.com/for-organizations)
        
        * [
            
            Employers](https://www.omadahealth.com/who-we-serve/employers)
        * [
            
            Health Plans](https://www.omadahealth.com/who-we-serve/health-plan)
        * [
            
            Benefit Consultants](https://www.omadahealth.com/who-we-serve/benefit-consultants)
        * [
            
            Health Systems & Providers](https://www.omadahealth.com/who-we-serve/health-systems-and-providers)
        * [
            
            Hear From Our Customers](https://www.omadahealth.com/about-us/customers)

    * [###### The Omada Platform
        
        Omada provides everything you need to streamline and improve care across multiple chronic conditions.
        
        Learn More](https://www.omadahealth.com/platform)
        
        ###### PROGRAMS
        
        * [
            
            Prediabetes](https://www.omadahealth.com/prediabetes)
        * [
            
            Diabetes](https://www.omadahealth.com/diabetes)
        * [
            
            Hypertension](https://www.omadahealth.com/hypertension)
        * [
            
            GLP-1 Care Track](https://www.omadahealth.com/glp-1-care-track)
        * [
            
            Musculoskeletal (MSK)](https://www.omadahealth.com/musculoskeletal)
        
        [###### Innovation
        
        With dynamic insights and analysis, the Insights Lab powers Omada's ability to meet every member's unique health needs.
        
        Learn More](https://www.omadahealth.com/insights-lab)

    * [###### Resource Center
        
        Access relevant trends, powerful insights, multi-disciplinary analysis, live-event learning, and more.
        
        Learn More](https://resourcecenter.omadahealth.com/)[](https://resourcecenter.omadahealth.com/)
        
        * [
            
            Case Studies](https://resourcecenter.omadahealth.com/case-studies)
        * [
            
            Whitepapers](https://resourcecenter.omadahealth.com/white-papers)
        * [
            
            Thought Leadership](https://resourcecenter.omadahealth.com/thought-leadership)
        * [
            
            Webinars & Events](https://resourcecenter.omadahealth.com/webinars-events)
        * [
            
            Peer-Reviewed Studies](https://resourcecenter.omadahealth.com/peer-reviewed-studies)
        * [
            
            Videos](https://resourcecenter.omadahealth.com/videos)
        * [
            
            Blog](https://resourcecenter.omadahealth.com/blog)

    * [###### About Omada
        
        Omada helps people change how they think about their health to experience powerful health changes.
        
        Learn More](https://www.omadahealth.com/about-us)
        
        * [
            
            Leadership](https://www.omadahealth.com/about-us/leadership-team)
        * [
            
            Careers](https://www.omadahealth.com/about-us/careers)
        * [
            
            Media Center](https://www.omadahealth.com/media-center-omada-health)
        * [
            
            Data Security](https://www.omadahealth.com/about-us/security)
        * [
            
            Contact Us](https://www.omadahealth.com/contact)

        * [###### The Omada Platform
            
            Duis mollis, est non commodo luctus, nisi erat porttitor ligula, eget lacinia odio sem necelit. Nullam quis risus eget urna mollis.
            
            Learn More](https://www.omadahealth.com/platform)
            
            ###### PROGRAMS
            
            * [
                
                Prediabetes](https://www.omadahealth.com/programs/prediabetes)
            * [
                
                Diabetes](https://www.omadahealth.com/programs/diabetes)
            * [
                
                Hypertension](https://www.omadahealth.com/programs/hypertension)
            * [
                
                Musculoskeletal (MSK)](https://www.omadahealth.com/programs/musuloskeletal)
            
            [###### Insights Lab
            
            Duis mollis, est non commodo luctus, nisi erat porttitor ligula, eget lacinia odio sem nec elit.
            
            Learn More](https://www.omadahealth.com/insights-lab)

        * [###### WHO WE SERVE
            
            Duis mollis, est non commodo luctus, nisi erat porttitor ligula, eget lacinia odio sem nec elit. Nullam quis risus eget urna mollis.](#)
            
            * [
                
                Employers](https://www.omadahealth.com/employers)
            * [
                
                Health Plans](https://www.omadahealth.com/health-plan)
            * [
                
                Benefit Consultants](https://www.omadahealth.com/benefit-consultants)

            [###### CONDITIONS WE TREAT
            
            Duis mollis, est non commodo luctus, nisi erat porttitor ligula, eget lacinia odio sem nec elit.](#)
            
            * [
                
                Prediabetes](https://www.omadahealth.com/for-individuals/prediabetes)
            * [
                
                Diabetes](https://www.omadahealth.com/for-individuals/diabetes)
            * [
                
                Hypertension](https://www.omadahealth.com/for-individuals/hypertension)
            * [
                
                Joint & Muscle Health](https://www.omadahealth.com/for-individuals/joint-and-muscle-health)
            
            [###### SUPPORT
            
            Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh.](#)
            
            * [
                
                Help Center](https://www.omadahealth.com/hc/en-us)
            * [
                
                FAQs](https://www.omadahealth.com/frequently-asked-questions)

        * [###### Resource Center
            
            Duis mollis, est non commodo luctus, nisi erat porttitor ligula, eget lacinia odio elit.](#)
            
            * [
                
                Blog](#)
            * [
                
                Whitepapers](#)
            * [
                
                Webinars and Events](#)
            * [
                
                Videos](#)
            * [
                
                Thought Leadership](#)
            * [
                
                Peer Reviewed Studies](#)
            * [
                
                Podcasts](#)

        * [###### About Omada
            
            Duis mollis, est non commodo luctus, nisi erat porttitor ligula, eget lacinia odio elit.](https://www.omadahealth.com/about-omada)
            
            * [
                
                About](https://www.omadahealth.com/about-omada)
            * [
                
                Leadership](https://www.omadahealth.com/leadership-team)
            * [
                
                Customers](https://www.omadahealth.com/customers)
            * [
                
                Careers](https://www.omadahealth.com/careers)
            * [
                
                Press & Editorial](#)
            * [
                
                Security](https://www.omadahealth.com/security)
            * [
                
                Contact Us](https://www.omadahealth.com/contact-us)

    * Search
    * Member Login

        * [###### The Omada Platform
            
            Duis mollis, est non commodo luctus, nisi erat porttitor ligula, eget lacinia odio sem necelit. Nullam quis risus eget urna mollis.
            
            Learn More](https://www.omadahealth.com/platform)
            
            ###### PROGRAMS
            
            * [
                
                Prediabetes](https://www.omadahealth.com/programs/prediabetes)
            * [
                
                Diabetes](https://www.omadahealth.com/programs/diabetes)
            * [
                
                Hypertension](https://www.omadahealth.com/programs/hypertension)
            * [
                
                Musculoskeletal (MSK)](https://www.omadahealth.com/programs/musuloskeletal)
            
            [###### Insights Lab
            
            Duis mollis, est non commodo luctus, nisi erat porttitor ligula, eget lacinia odio sem nec elit.
            
            Learn More](https://www.omadahealth.com/insights-lab)

        * [###### WHO WE SERVE
            
            Duis mollis, est non commodo luctus, nisi erat porttitor ligula, eget lacinia odio sem nec elit. Nullam quis risus eget urna mollis.](#)
            
            * [
                
                Employers](https://www.omadahealth.com/employers)
            * [
                
                Health Plans](https://www.omadahealth.com/health-plan)
            * [
                
                Benefit Consultants](https://www.omadahealth.com/benefit-consultants)

            [###### CONDITIONS WE TREAT
            
            Duis mollis, est non commodo luctus, nisi erat porttitor ligula, eget lacinia odio sem nec elit.](#)
            
            * [
                
                Prediabetes](https://www.omadahealth.com/for-individuals/prediabetes)
            * [
                
                Diabetes](https://www.omadahealth.com/for-individuals/diabetes)
            * [
                
                Hypertension](https://www.omadahealth.com/for-individuals/hypertension)
            * [
                
                Joint & Muscle Health](https://www.omadahealth.com/for-individuals/joint-and-muscle-health)
            
            [###### SUPPORT
            
            Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh.](#)
            
            * [
                
                Help Center](https://www.omadahealth.com/hc/en-us)
            * [
                
                FAQs](https://www.omadahealth.com/frequently-asked-questions)

        * [###### Resource Center
            
            Duis mollis, est non commodo luctus, nisi erat porttitor ligula, eget lacinia odio elit.](#)
            
            * [
                
                Blog](#)
            * [
                
                Whitepapers](#)
            * [
                
                Webinars and Events](#)
            * [
                
                Videos](#)
            * [
                
                Thought Leadership](#)
            * [
                
                Peer Reviewed Studies](#)
            * [
                
                Podcasts](#)

        * [###### About Omada
            
            Duis mollis, est non commodo luctus, nisi erat porttitor ligula, eget lacinia odio elit.](https://www.omadahealth.com/about-omada)
            
            * [
                
                About](https://www.omadahealth.com/about-omada)
            * [
                
                Leadership](https://www.omadahealth.com/leadership-team)
            * [
                
                Customers](https://www.omadahealth.com/customers)
            * [
                
                Careers](https://www.omadahealth.com/careers)
            * [
                
                Press & Editorial](#)
            * [
                
                Security](https://www.omadahealth.com/security)
            * [
                
                Contact Us](https://www.omadahealth.com/contact-us)

    * Search
    * Member Login

Privacy Policy
==============

Effective Date: April 1, 2024

TABLE OF CONTENTS:

* * *

**­**
-----

Privacy Policy
--------------

Welcome to Omada. We take your privacy seriously, and we want you to be familiar with how we collect, use, and share personal information from you. Please carefully read this privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) because it contains important information about your legal rights. 

This Privacy Policy forms a part of the [Terms of Use](https://www.omadahealth.com/terms-of-use), which are binding terms between you and us. In this Privacy Policy, “us,” “we,” and “Omada” refer to Omada Health, Inc. and its affiliates and subsidiaries (and the Professional Entities described in the footnote below). Any capitalized terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy will have the meanings given to those terms in the Terms of Use. 

This Privacy Policy applies to your access to and use of the following services, which we refer to together as the “Services”:

* our digitally based health care programs (the “Omada Programs”);1
* our mobile applications, including Omada and Omada for Joint & Muscle Health (the “Apps”);
* the websites that we operate (including [go.omadahealth.com](https://go.omadahealth.com/), [www.omadahealth.com](https://www.omadahealth.com/), and www.physera.com) (the “Sites”); and 
* all related services and features that we provide.

Throughout this Privacy Policy, we distinguish between individuals that use different aspects of our Services with the following terms:2

* “Omada Members” refers to individuals that apply for, register for, and/or enroll in one or more Omada Programs as they interact with the Omada Program(s) and/or uses the App(s); and
* “Site Visitors” refers to individuals that visit the Sites and other aspects of our Services while not interacting with the Omada Program and/or using the App(s) as Omada Members.

In this Privacy Policy, we describe how we collect, maintain, use, disclose, and process certain information about you. By accessing or using any aspects of the Services, you consent to this Privacy Policy and to our collection, maintenance, use, disclosure, and processing of Personal Information, all as described in this Privacy Policy. 

If you are an Omada Member, you also expressly acknowledge that you have read and understood our [Notice of HIPAA Privacy Practices](https://www.omadahealth.com/hipaa-notice). Our Notice of HIPAA Privacy Practices describes how we may use and disclose health information that we receive as we deliver health care to you through the Omada Program(s), including in the application process for Omada Programs. We use this information for treatment, payment, or health care operations and for other purposes that are permitted or required by applicable laws, including the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act of 1996, as amended from time to time (“HIPAA”). For Omada Members, to the extent there is any conflict between this Privacy Policy and the Notice of HIPAA Privacy Practices, the Notice of HIPAA Privacy Practices will control.

In addition, for Omada Members and Site Visitors located in California, Colorado, Connecticut, Utah, and Virginia, additional information regarding our privacy practices under state-specific privacy laws is available [here](https://www.omadahealth.com/state-privacy).

### WHAT IS THE PURPOSE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY?

Protection and use of Personal Information are important parts of our business. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, maintain, use, disclose, and process your Personal Information, which includes, among other things, how we gather, store, evaluate, modify, delete, combine, share, and transfer that information. 

We will not rent or sell your Personal Information, and we will not permit the business partners that we engage to provide our Services to rent or sell your Personal Information either. In addition, we will not share your Personal Information with third parties for their own purposes, except where authorized, directed, or instructed by you (as described below) and except, for Omada Members, where those disclosures are described in our [Notice of HIPAA Privacy Practices](https://www.omadahealth.com/hipaa-notice) (such as disclosures of Protected Health Information to your other health care providers or to other entities that have certain relationships with you under HIPAA). We may transfer Personal Information in connection with a transfer of part of our business, but if we do, we would require that the successor entity comply with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.

In some cases, you may instruct us to share information with non-affiliated companies. For example, you may direct, instruct, or authorize us to share information, including sensitive health information, with Apple HealthKit or similar services from Google or with other online companies with which you interact. When you choose to instruct us to share information with non-affiliated companies, visit websites from Third-Party Providers or use Third-Party Offerings, those companies will not be bound by any of the promises in our Terms of Use, Privacy Policy, or Notice of HIPAA Privacy Practices. These promises and terms do not apply to the practices of any third parties that we do not control or the products or services that they provide. For more information on Third-Party Offerings and Third-Party Providers, please review the Terms of Use. You are solely responsible for understanding the terms of use and privacy policies of those non-affiliated companies and how they use and maintain your information.

### WHAT DOES THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVER?

This Privacy Policy covers how we use and disclose Personal Information that we gather from you, beginning at the time that you first access one of our Sites or Apps and on an ongoing basis as you use or access the Sites, the Apps, the Omada Programs, or other aspects of our Services. As a healthcare provider, Omada is also dedicated to maintaining the privacy and integrity of the protected health information that we receive from Omada Members through online clinical screeners or as part of applications for or participation in the Omada Programs, including the health information we collect through digital devices that are used in connection with the Omada Programs. 

Personal Information – In General

In this Privacy Policy, we use the term “Personal Information” to refer to information we gather that could be used to identify or contact you and any identifiable information we gather concerning your use or potential use of the Services. Examples of Personal Information include your first and last name, your personal profile information, your email address or other contact information, and all User Submissions. Your Personal Information that we receive may include “personal information” as that term is defined by relevant laws and regulations, including current laws in California, Colorado, Connecticut, Utah, and Virginia, where those laws apply. Residents of these states may refer to our [Supplemental State Privacy Notice](https://www.omadahealth.com/state-privacy) for more information on their rights.

Protected Health Information

In this Privacy Policy, we use the terms “Protected Health Information” or “PHI” to refer to the subset of Personal Information that we create, receive, transmit, or maintain as part of an Omada Member’s registration, application for, or participation in an Omada Program or that an Omada Member supplies as part of our online clinical screeners, where that information relates to (a) the Omada Member’s past, present, or future physical or mental health or condition; (b) the provision of healthcare to the Omada Member; or (c) the Omada Member’s past, present, or future payment for that healthcare. Federal and state law afford Omada Members certain rights with respect to any access to, use of, or disclosure of their PHI. In addition, our [Notice of HIPAA Privacy Practices](https://www.omadahealth.com/hipaa-notice) provides additional important information about how we may use and disclose PHI from Omada Members. 

Your privacy is important to us, and we are committed to carefully managing your Personal Information in connection with the Services that we provide. 

### WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

We collect Personal Information from you and certain devices that you may use, as further described below. For Omada Members, this includes information collected through clinical screeners, applications, registrations, eligibility checks (including those on our Sites and in our Apps and those available through business partners that we work with to enable individuals to check coverage for Omada Programs directly from those sites), and your use of the Apps and the Omada Programs. For Site Visitors, this includes Personal Information that you may provide to us through the Sites. For both Omada Members and Site Visitors, we also receive some Personal Information that is collected automatically, as further described below. We may also collect Personal Information through third-party sources (including data brokers, as that term is defined under applicable laws), such as email service providers. We also collect Personal Information in connection with inquiries you may make through the Sites, the Omada Programs, or the Apps. Collection starts from the time that you initially access our Services.

Information that we gather enables us:

* to provide you with the Services, 
* to manage Omada Members’ accounts,
* to send you communications regarding the services we offer, 
* to respond to your inquiries, 
* to obtain your feedback on our Services,
* to understand who is using our Services and how the Services are performing,
* to otherwise review behavior and activity of Omada Members and Site Visitors, 
* to personalize and improve our Services, 
* to conduct research activities, 
* to manage the security of the Services, and
* to fulfill any requirements imposed on us by applicable laws and regulations.

From time to time, we may obtain information about you from third parties and may use, add to, or update Personal Information that we have about you using information obtained from those third parties. For example, we may obtain contact information from third parties or use third-party information to confirm contact or financial information, to verify your coverage eligibility for an Omada Program, or to better understand your interests by associating demographic information with the information that you have provided. As a healthcare provider, we may also receive information about Omada Members from other entities in the healthcare system, such as an Omada Member’s other healthcare providers, an Omada Member’s insurance company, or health data exchanges that enable those entities to share Protected Health Information for legally permitted purposes. 

In some cases, you will provide Personal Information to us in connection with your use of the Services, and if you are an Omada Member, that Personal Information may include Protected Health Information. In other cases, we may collect this information automatically when you visit or interact with the Sites, the Apps, or other aspects of the Services. We provide more detail below on the types of Personal Information that you provide and the types of Personal Information that we collect automatically: 

Personal Information that You Provide to Us

Information that You Provide Directly. We receive and store any information that you enter on our Sites or through one of our Apps; information collected through clinical screeners, applications, registrations, eligibility checks (including those on our Sites and in our Apps and those available through business partners that we work with to enable individuals to check coverage for Omada Programs directly from those sites); information that you share with us by email or phone; and any other information that you provide to us through the Services. Personal Information that you provide may include your full name, gender, username and password, contact information (e.g., your phone number, your email address and the email address of your contacts, home and business postal addresses), certain health information (e.g., weight, pre-existing medical conditions, blood glucose and blood pressure readings, information concerning your exercise, sleep, injuries, pain levels, prior courses of treatment, messages with our Care Teams, and other activities), health insurance information, User Submissions (as further described in our [Terms of Use](https://www.omadahealth.com/terms-of-use)), credit card and/or other payment information (where applicable for participants who pay for their own participation in the Services), and any other information or data that you provide when using our Services. If you are an Omada Member, you may also participate in video consultations as part of an Omada Program, and you acknowledge and agree that we may record these consultations for training purposes.

Information You Provide through Omada-Supplied Devices. If you are an Omada Member, we may enable you to share information with us in connection with the Omada Programs through digital equipment that we provide to you that assists you in tracking changes in your health or fitness. In many cases, the equipment supplies that information automatically to us and the applicable Omada Program. We refer to these devices as “Omada-Supplied Devices.” Most Omada-Supplied Devices are pre-configured to supply information to us and will share information about Omada Members and their health without requiring additional authorizations from the Omada Members. Examples of Personal Information that we may receive from Omada-Supplied Devices include weight, blood glucose readings, and blood pressure readings. You can find more information about Omada-Supplied Devices in our [Terms of Use](https://www.omadahealth.com/terms-of-use). 

Information that You Direct, Instruct, or Authorize Third-Party Data Sources to Provide. We also may enable you to share information with us from third parties who have received your information because you subscribe to or participate in their services. We refer to these sources of information as “Third-Party Data Sources.” For Omada Members, Third-Party Data Sources may include any digital equipment, such as blood glucose monitors or blood pressure monitors, that you already possess or that you later acquire on your own and not from us (“Third-Party Health Devices”). We may receive Personal Information about Omada Members through Third-Party Health Devices if the Omada Member enters that information manually through the Apps or the Sites or enables the device to supply information to us automatically. In addition to Third-Party Health Devices, Third-Party Data Sources may also include other third-party sources of data that you direct, instruct, or authorize to deliver information to us. For Omada Members, these Third-Party Data Sources may include external health care providers that have provided the Omada Member with a referral or a prescription and shared that information with Omada at the Omada Member’s direction, authorization, or instruction; health and wellness services such as Apple HealthKit and similar services from Google that the Omada Member may direct, instruct, or authorize to deliver information to us; or other digital companies that may assist Omada Members in checking their coverage for, applying for, or enrolling in Omada Program and that Omada Members direct, instruct, or authorize to deliver information to us. Examples of Omada Member Personal Information that we may receive from Third-Party Data Sources, including Third-Party Health Devices, include weight, blood glucose readings, blood pressure readings, and information concerning exercise, sleep, and other activities. You can find more information about Third-Party Data Sources, including Third-Party Health Devices, in our Terms of Use.

We will use the Personal Information that you provide for the purposes described above (and any other purposes intrinsic to the Services that you use) and to provide you with an engaging and personalized experience in using the Services. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but if you do make that choice, we may be unable to provide you with access to or use of many of our features. 

Personal Information Shared with Us as Your Health Care Provider from Others

If you are an Omada Member, we may receive Personal Information, including Protected Health Information, about you from other parties in the health care system that are legally permitted to share that information with us as your health care provider under HIPAA. For example, third-party providers or health plans that have provided you with services, such as health insurance, prescriptions, or referrals, may share Personal Information, including Protected Health Information, about you with us. We may also obtain Personal Information, including Protected Health Information, about Omada Members from health information exchanges available to health care providers like us for purposes such as treatment and health care operations. This type of sharing is described in more detail in our [Notice of HIPAA Privacy Practices](https://www.omadahealth.com/hipaa-notice). 

Other Personal Information that We Have Licensed from Third Parties

We may license or otherwise collect information, including email addresses, other contact information, and other Personal Information, from third parties such as email database providers, content syndication platforms, or industry event hosts. If we email you using information collected from these sources, you may opt out of those emails by following the included instructions to unsubscribe in the same manner as described elsewhere in this Privacy Policy. If we combine or associate information from other sources with personal information or Protected Health Information that we collect through the Service, we will treat the combined information as Personal Information or Protected Health Information accordingly, in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

Personal Information Collected Automatically

In addition to any information that you provide to us through the Services or that we receive from others, we and our third-party service providers may use a variety of technologies that store or collect certain information from you automatically (or passively) when you visit or interact with the Sites, the Apps, or other aspects of the Services (“Usage Information”). This Usage Information may be stored or accessed using technologies downloaded to your device whenever you visit or interact with the Services. Examples of Usage Information include: your IP address, other unique device identifiers assigned to your device that allow our computers to recognize you, details of your device’s characteristics and functionality (e.g., browser, operating system, mobile network information), the areas within the Site, the Apps, or other aspects of the Services that you visit and your activities there, your device’s location, and certain other data regarding your device. 

To the extent we associate Usage Information with your Personal Information or Usage Information includes identifiable information, we will treat it as Personal Information. In addition, if you are an Omada Member, to the extent we associate Usage Information with your PHI or collect Usage Information through your application for or participation in Omada Programs, we protect that information as PHI under our [Notice of HIPAA Privacy Practices](https://www.omadahealth.com/hipaa-notice). 

Information from Your Browser or Device

We automatically receive and record Usage Information from your browser on our server logs whenever you interact with the Site, the Apps, or other aspects of the Services. We may use this Usage Information to provide you with customer service and support. We also may use this Usage Information to recognize you when you arrive at the Site from an external link, such as a link appearing on a third-party site or in an email generated by us. We discuss this type of technology in more detail under “Tracking Technologies” below. Our Services also collect Usage Information to determine how often Site Visitors and Omada Members use parts of the Site, the Apps, or other aspects of the Services so that we can improve our Services and strive to ensure that the Services appeal to as many users and customers as possible. 

You may set your browser to refuse or disable these data collection methods, but doing so may change your experience with the Sites, the Apps, or other aspects of the Services, diminish certain aspects of the Services’ functionality, or render certain features inoperable. For example, the Sites may not recognize or respond to your browser with “do not track” technologies employed.

Email Communications and Notifications

We may receive a confirmation when you open an email or notification from us if your device supports this type of confirmation. We use this confirmation to make our messages more interesting and helpful. If you are an Omada Member, you may adjust your email and notification preferences in the Apps, and you may change what types of notifications you receive on your mobile device by adjusting the device’s settings. You also may opt out of any emails we send that do not relate to an Omada Member’s account by following the included instructions to unsubscribe. If you would like assistance in unsubscribing from email communications, please contact us in any of the manners described at the end of this Privacy Policy. Please keep in mind that, by opting out of further email communications after you enroll in an Omada Program, you may limit program reminders and other valuable program content and components.

Tracking Technologies

We may use various tracking methods or technologies (“Tracking Technologies”) to store or collect your Usage Information, including information about your visits to or interactions with our Sites, the Apps, and other aspects of the Services. We use Tracking Technologies for a variety of purposes we believe to be necessary or helpful in improving or assessing the performance of the Services (for example, as part of our analytic practices) or in offering you enhanced functionality (for example, to identify Omada Members when they sign in, to keep track of your specified preferences, or to help ensure that the security of Omada Members’ accounts have not been compromised).

Tracking Technologies may include the following technologies and methods as well as any subsequent technologies and methods later developed to perform similar functions:

Cookies. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your device through your browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to tell us how and when you visit pages in our Site or other aspects of the Services. We use cookies to enhance the experiences of Omada Members and Site Visitors by understanding how they engage with and navigate our Site and the Services. Regular cookies may be disabled or removed generally by adjusting certain settings available as part of most browsers. In some (but not all) cases, these tools can block those cookies in the future. Each browser that you use would need to be set separately, and different browsers offer different functionality and options in this regard. In addition, these tools may not be effective for certain types of cookies (e.g., Adobe Flash or HTML5 cookies). Your ability to limit cookies when you revisit our Site or Services is subject to your browser settings and limitations. Please note that, if you disable or remove cookies on your device, some parts of our Sites or other aspects of our Services may not function properly.

Embedded Scripts. An embedded script is programming code designed to collect information about your interactions with the Sites, the Apps, and other aspects of our Services, such as a link that you may click on. Embedded scripts are temporarily downloaded onto your device. Embedded scripts remain active only while you are connected to the Services and are then deactivated or deleted.

Web Beacons. The Services may also include small graphic images or other web programming code called “web beacons” (also known as “1×1 GIFs” or “clear GIFs”). Any electronic image or other web programming code inserted into a page or email can act as a web beacon, and web beacons may be invisible to you. Web beacons and similar technologies may be used for a number of purposes, including to count Site Visitors and Omada Members visiting the Services, to count how many sent emails were opened, to count how many articles or links were viewed, or to monitor how Site Visitors and Omada Members navigate the Services.

This Privacy Policy refers only to the use of cookies and other Tracking Technologies by Omada and does not cover the use of any Tracking Technologies by third-party advertisers or any other third parties. To confirm how any third party collects or uses your information, please refer to that third party’s website. As we mentioned above, we will not rent or sell your Personal Information to third parties or share your Personal Information with third parties for their own purposes, except where directed, instructed, or authorized by you.

### WHO OWNS THE PERSONAL INFORMATION YOU DISCLOSE TO COMPANY?

You retain all ownership or license rights that you possess in your User Submissions (including any Personal Information and PHI), provided that when you use the Services or otherwise disclose or direct, instruct, or authorize others to disclose any User Submissions to us, you grant us a license to those User Submissions as described in our [Terms of Use](https://www.omadahealth.com/terms-of-use), this Privacy Policy, and, for Omada Members, our [Notice of HIPAA Privacy Practices](https://www.omadahealth.com/hipaa-notice).

### WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE SHARE?

The following sections describe certain circumstances when we may share your Personal Information:

Information from Omada Members that May Be Shared with Other Omada Members

If as an Omada Member, you access or use any Omada Program that includes a group or community component, other Omada Members will have access to a range of Personal Information that you may choose to share, as further described below. These other Omada Members may include your co-workers or other acquaintances. By accessing or using any such Omada Program, you authorize Omada to disclose to other Omada Members that you are clinically eligible for the Services and that you participate in relevant aspects of the Services, which may indicate that you meet the clinical enrollment criteria for relevant aspects of the Services and may identify you as living with or at risk for certain chronic diseases or conditions. 

If you enroll in an Omada Program, on your Omada Member profile page, you may provide information about your health, symptoms, and treatments, your feelings about your health information and/or yourself, or any other information about yourself. You may also upload pictures, videos, and stories to your Omada Member profile page. Any information that you choose to include in creating, completing, or updating your Omada Member profile page may be viewable by other Omada Members, and other Omada Members may be able to post comments and view posted comments on your Omada Member profile page. For Omada Members, certain summary information about your participation, such as the number of days in your latest weigh-in or activity streak, your general percentage of progress toward your goals, and your last activity date in the Omada Program (“Summary Information”) may also be visible to other Omada Members, but this Summary Information will not include personal biometrics such as your current weight or device readings. If you are an Omada Member, you must provide us with your legal name, but you are permitted to choose a nickname and/or a picture other than a photo of yourself for display in your Omada Member profile page viewable to other Omada Members. Your Care Team, however, will know your legal name.

In addition, if you are an Omada Member, in connection with your participation in an Omada Program, we may place you in an online peer group, and you may choose to enroll in other group-based communities that we may offer. The Site, the Apps, and other aspects of the Services may include the ability to interact with discussion boards, chat rooms, community pages, profile pages, bulletin boards, blogs, instant messaging or other messaging services, activities, polls, games, and other communication forums to which you post or otherwise make information or materials available (“Groups”). Please note that any information, text, and images that you post or disclose on or through the Groups may be visible to the present and future individuals in those groups or communities. For Omada Members, your Omada Member ID, Omada Member profile photo, and related Summary Information may also be viewable to other Omada Members when you send messages or when you disclose information on or through these Groups generally.

We take great care to protect your privacy, but please remember that we cannot control how other Omada Members will use or disclose any information that you share on your Omada Member profile page or disclose to Groups. We urge you to exercise discretion and caution when deciding to disclose information, including your health information and other Personal Information, on your Omada Member profile page, through a Group, or otherwise through the Services. 

### WE EXPRESSLY DISCLAIM ANY RESPONSIBILITY FOR THE USE BY OTHERS OF ANY INFORMATION, INCLUDING PERSONAL INFORMATION, THAT IS DISCLOSED TO OTHERS BY YOU OR ON YOUR BEHALF ON YOUR OMADA MEMBER PROFILE PAGE OR TO GROUPS OR OTHER PUBLIC-FACING FEATURES OF THE SERVICES, INCLUDING DISCUSSION BOARDS, CHAT ROOMS, MESSAGING SERVICES, OR OTHER GROUPS DESCRIBED ABOVE. BY DISCLOSING ANY OF YOUR INFORMATION THROUGH THESE FEATURES, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND ACCEPT ANY RISK AND DAMAGE ARISING FROM THE DISCLOSURE OF THAT INFORMATION.

Communications in Response to User Submissions

As part of the Services, you will receive from us email and other communications relating to your User Submissions. By posting User Submissions, you acknowledge and agree that we may send you email, text messages, phone calls, and other communications that we determine in our sole discretion relate to your User Submissions.

Information Shared with Our Agents

We employ other people and companies to perform tasks on our behalf, and we must share your information with them in order to provide products and/or services to you. For example, you may check your eligibility or begin applications for Omada Programs through connected capabilities that our business partners offer as our agents, and we may share certain information with those business partners as they enable those checks and related services. By accessing or using the Services, you consent to and authorize Omada to disclose Personal Information about you to our authorized personnel and administrators, including, for Omada Members, our Care Teams and other authorized agents. We require any people or companies assisting us with tasks to agree to appropriate privacy and security assurances and limitations on this use of your Personal Information. Unless we have your authorization or consent, we do not permit these agents to rent or sell any of the Personal Information about you that they receive from us or to use the Personal Information for their own purposes. In addition, to the extent we share PHI with these agents, we only share with them the amount of PHI that is minimally necessary to assist us, and our contracts with these companies require them to comply with HIPAA. 

Information Shared with Other Entities Permitted by HIPAA, including Sponsors, Third-Party Administrators, External Health Care Providers, and their Agents

If you are an Omada Member, we may, in our sole discretion, share, transfer, or otherwise disclose certain of your Personal Information and PHI to entities that are authorized to receive that information for legally permitted purposes under HIPAA. 

Under certain circumstances and subject to certain limitations specified under HIPAA or other applicable law, we may share, transfer, or otherwise disclose Personal Information and PHI to the companies paying for your participation in an Omada Program, including their agents and third-party administrators. 

We also may share, transfer, or otherwise disclose Personal Information and PHI to other health care providers or entities that have certain relationships with you under HIPAA (including their agents), either directly or through health information exchanges available to health care providers like us. 

This type of sharing is described in more detail in our [Notice of HIPAA Privacy Practices](https://www.omadahealth.com/hipaa-notice). We only share Protected Health Information from Omada Members in accordance with HIPAA and other applicable legal requirements.

Promotional Offers and Communication Preferences

From time to time, we may send you promotional communications. You may manage your receipt of these email communications by clicking on the "unsubscribe" link located on the bottom of the email. We will process opt-out requests within the time required by law, if not faster, but you may receive additional offers as we process your request. If you are an Omada Member, you may also update your preferences for communications in your Omada Member profile. Please note that Omada Members cannot opt out of receiving certain transactional emails related to their account (such as an email notifying you of an update to these terms). 

We will never disclose your Personal Information to other businesses for their own purposes unless you direct, instruct, or authorize us to do so, except, for Omada Members, where those disclosures are described in our [Notice of HIPAA Privacy Practices](https://www.omadahealth.com/hipaa-notice) (such as disclosures of Protected Health Information to your other health care providers or to other entities that have certain relationships with you under HIPAA). In certain circumstances, such as when Site Visitors register for a webinar, you may share your Personal Information with us and with a third-party co-sponsor simultaneously, which we will make clear. As mentioned above, you may choose to share information with non-affiliated companies or to direct, instruct, or authorize us to share information about you with non-affiliated companies, in which case, those companies will not be bound by any of the promises in our Terms of Use, Privacy Policy, or Notice of HIPAA Privacy Practices. You are solely responsible for understanding the terms of use and privacy policies of those non-affiliated companies and how they use and maintain your information.

Information Available to App Providers

By downloading any of the Apps from an App Provider, such as the Apple App Store or Google Play, please note that the App Provider and its agents may be able to identify you as an Omada Member or other user of our Services.

Information Shared with Other Businesses We Do Not Control 

To provide you with the optimal user experience, our Services may enable you to contact third-party businesses for related services or products. For example, we may enable Omada Members to contact external, third-party health care providers that can provide referrals for treatment or prescriptions. In other situations, we may provide services or sell products jointly with affiliated businesses. You should be able to recognize when a third-party business is associated with your transactions. 

Sharing at Your Direction. In certain circumstances, you may choose to instruct, direct, or authorize us to share information with these third-party businesses pursuant to their own terms of use and privacy policies. In these circumstances, you are solely responsible for understanding the terms of use and privacy policies of those businesses and how they use and maintain your information. 

Sharing When Permitted by Law. In other circumstances, where these third-party businesses are authorized to receive PHI about you for permitted purposes under HIPAA, we may share, transfer, or otherwise disclose certain of your PHI to these third-party businesses, as further described earlier in this Privacy Policy and in our Notice of HIPAA Privacy Practices. In these circumstances, those third-party businesses will be responsible for using and protecting your PHI in compliance with HIPAA. 

In either case, these third-party businesses will not be bound by any of the promises in Omada’s Terms of Use, Privacy Policy, or Notice of HIPAA Privacy Practices.

Referrals to Family, Colleagues, and Friends

From time to time, we may ask or invite you to refer our Services to family members, colleagues, or friends. We ask you to limit your invitations to people in your inner circle that may have an interest in our Services. In these cases, it is your responsibility to ensure that these persons are indeed family members or people with whom you have a personal relationship (based on frequency of communication, sharing of interests or opinions, etc.). If we refer one of these persons to the Services, we may inform them that you have suggested that they may be interested in trying our Services. If they request that we do not contact them again, we will not contact them again.

Our Business Transfers

We reserve the right to disclose and transfer all Personal Information to an operator of the Sites or of any of the Apps, Programs, or applicable databases, provided that the operator agrees to be bound by the applicable terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. We also reserve the right to disclose and transfer all Personal Information to a successor in interest of Omada in connection with a merger, consolidation, restructuring, or change of control, the sale of substantially all of our interests and/or assets, or another organizational change (including during the course of any due diligence process), provided that the successor entity agrees to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.

Protection of Omada and Others

We may release your Personal Information when we believe in good faith that releasing that information is necessary to comply with applicable law or the subpoena or warrant of a court of law or similar authority with jurisdiction, to enforce our conditions of use and other agreements, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Omada, our Care Teams, our other employees, Omada Members, Site Visitors, or others. We may exchange information with other companies and organizations to detect, suppress, or protect against fraud and for credit risk reduction. If necessary and required by law, we will disclose any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your Personal Information, including, without limitation, breaches of your unencrypted, electronically stored “personal information” or “medical information” (as defined by applicable laws). To the extent permitted by applicable laws, we may make these disclosures to you via email or a conspicuous posting on your private profile in the Services in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, so long as this is consistent with the legitimate needs of law enforcement and any other measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system.

De-identified Data

As described in our [Terms of Use](https://www.omadahealth.com/terms-of-use), we may de-identify the User Submissions that you share with us, including any Personal Information, or otherwise process them so that they are no longer attributable to you without additional information (“De-identified Data”). We may use that De-identified Data without restriction in any way allowed by law. For example, we might use De-identified Data to understand, evaluate, or modify the Services, to generate statistical information about the Services that we share with our customers and other third parties who are evaluating, analyzing, accrediting, or researching Omada’s programs, or for our other business purposes. When an applicable law requires that we use a particular method of de-identifying data or rendering it no longer attributable to you, we will comply with that law. Otherwise, we may use a method that is appropriate under the circumstances and would not reasonably identify you. 

### IS MY PERSONAL INFORMATION SECURE?

We employ industry-standard administrative, physical, and technical measures designed to safeguard and protect information under our control from unauthorized access, use, and disclosure. In addition, when we collect, maintain, use, disclose, and process your Personal Information, we will do so using systems and processes consistent with the information privacy and security requirements of applicable federal and state laws, including, for Omada Members, HIPAA.

Your individual Omada Member account is also protected by a password for your privacy and security. To help avoid unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information, we suggest that you safeguard your password appropriately, limit access to your devices and browsers, and sign off after you have finished accessing your account.

In addition, to the extent that you are an Omada Member and your device permits our Apps to send you push notifications, we may send you push notifications that include Personal Information and, in limited instances, PHI that is not encrypted on your device. Similarly, to the extent you are an Omada Member and you provide us with permission to send you text messages, we may send you text messages that include Personal Information and, in limited instances, PHI that is not encrypted. Depending on your device settings, push notifications and text messages may be visible to other people who encounter your device. In most cases, you can opt out of receiving push notifications or change the visibility settings for push notifications and text messages by adjusting the settings on your device. To the extent that you do not change these settings, you agree to receive push notifications and authorized text messages and to be responsible for the security and confidentiality of any information displayed in push notifications and text messages on your devices. We are not responsible for Personal Information or other information that others may encounter because they obtain access to your password(s), your devices, your email accounts, your browsers, or your browser history.

The Services may contain links to Third-Party Offerings (as further described in the [Terms of Use](https://www.omadahealth.com/terms-of-use)). When you access any Third-Party Offerings, you do so at your own risk, and you understand and agree that you are solely responsible for reading and understanding any terms of use and/or privacy policies that apply to those Third-Party Offerings. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices of any Third-Party Offerings, and we are not responsible or liable for the availability, performance, technical failures, content, accuracy, efficacy, appropriateness, safety, legality, security, or any other aspect of Third-Party Offerings.  

We exercise great care to protect your Personal Information. However, we cannot ensure the security or confidentiality of any Systems or Connections that you use to transmit information to us. For example, we cannot ensure that your email or your mobile phone or any other personal device is secure. In addition, communication lines used to transmit emails and text messages do not have the same security features that are built into our Services. For more information on your Systems and Connections, please review the [Terms of Use](https://www.omadahealth.com/terms-of-use). 

Although we take great care to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee that criminals or others acting unlawfully will not succeed in efforts to undermine our security measures. Unauthorized entry to, access to, or use of our systems or locations, hardware or software failure, loss, and other factors may compromise the security of your information at any time. 

If you have reason to believe that your data or your interactions with us are no longer secure or if you have questions related to privacy or data security, you may contact us in any of the manners described at the end of this Privacy Policy. 

### WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION CAN I ACCESS AND CORRECT?

If you are an Omada Member, you can access certain information about you described below through the App or otherwise through the Omada Program in order to view, and in certain situations, update that information. This list may change as the Services change.

* First and last name
* Account and Omada Member profile information (e.g., nickname and picture)
* Email address
* Mailing address
* Phone number
* Username and password
* Communication preferences (e.g., email and push notifications)
* Data concerning your weight, activity, food tracking, blood glucose measurements, blood pressure measurements, or health goals (where applicable to the Omada Programs in which you participate).

Omada may choose not to accept a change to certain clinical information if doing so would cause a clinically inaccurate record. For more on the right to correct or amend your PHI, please refer to our [Notice of HIPAA Privacy Practices](https://www.omadahealth.com/hipaa-notice).

If you are an Omada Member, you also have the right to receive a copy of your PHI as is described in our Notice of HIPAA Privacy Practices. If you are a Site Visitor but not an Omada Member, you can access certain information about you by contacting us in any of the manners described below at the end of this Privacy Policy or as otherwise required by the applicable law, including as described in the [Supplemental State Privacy Notice](https://www.omadahealth.com/state-privacy). 

In order to help us maintain your information and ensure that it is accurate and up to date, please update your information if it changes or inform us promptly in any of the manners described at the end of this Privacy Policy so that we can make the appropriate changes. When you update information, we often maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records.

### WHAT RIGHTS AND CHOICES DO I HAVE REGARDING MY PERSONAL INFORMATION?

Choosing Not to Disclose

You may choose not to disclose information to us, even though that information may be required to take advantage of certain features of the Services. 

Requesting Information

You also have the right to request certain information from us, specifically:

* a copy of the Personal Information that we collect from you,
* a description of the specific pieces of Personal Information that we collect from you,
* a description of the categories of Personal Information that we collect from you (which you can find in this Privacy Policy),
* a description of the sources of Personal Information that we collect from you (which you can find in this Privacy Policy), and 
* a description of the purposes for which we gather Personal Information from you (which you can find in this Privacy Policy and, for Omada Members, in our Notice of HIPAA Privacy Practices). 

Omada Members also have rights concerning our access to and use of their Protected Health Information, which are described more fully in our [Notice of HIPAA Privacy Practices](https://www.omadahealth.com/hipaa-notice).

You also have the right to request information about any of your Personal Information we may sell or share with third parties for their own purposes. For your convenience and to avoid any need to request this information from us, we have confirmed in this Privacy Policy that we will not rent or sell your Personal Information. In addition, we will not share your Personal Information with third parties for their own purposes, except where we obtain your permission (as described above) and except, for Omada Members, where those disclosures are described in our [Notice of HIPAA Privacy Practices](https://www.omadahealth.com/hipaa-notice) (such as disclosures of Protected Health Information to your other health care providers or to other entities that have certain relationships with you under HIPAA).   

To request information from us or to obtain additional information and instructions for exercising your rights to obtain information, please contact us in any of the manners described at the end of this Privacy Policy.

Unsubscribing from Communications

You may unsubscribe from communications from us, but please keep in mind that, if you are an Omada Member, by opting out of further communications, you may limit program reminders and other valuable program content and components. In addition, even if you do not want to receive legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Policy, those legal notices will still govern your use of the Services, and you are responsible for reviewing legal notices for changes. When you receive an email from us, you can opt out of receiving further emails by following the included instructions to unsubscribe. In addition, if you are an Omada Member, you may adjust your email preferences in the Apps. If you would like assistance in unsubscribing from email communications or if you do not wish to receive mail, phone calls, or text messages from us you may indicate this preference by contacting us in any of the manners described at the end of this Privacy Policy. We will process your request within a reasonable time, but please note that you may receive additional emails as we process your request.

Deleting Your Account and/or Deleting Personal Information

As a health care provider, we are required by law to maintain the Personal Information, including any PHI, that we receive from Omada Members as a business record. As a result, we cannot eliminate User Submissions or other Personal Information from Omada Members from our records. Certain features required by the Apple App Store or Google Play may require that we include a process for requesting account deletion. While we can assist you in closing your account and no longer sharing Personal Information with us, our regulatory compliance obligations as a health care provider will require that we will retain Personal Information for the duration required by law. However, even if you are an Omada Member and you stop using our Services for any reason (including closing your account), we will protect any User Submissions and other Personal Information that we maintain in accordance with our [Terms of Use](https://www.omadahealth.com/terms-of-use), this Privacy Policy, and our [Notice of HIPAA Privacy Practices](https://www.omadahealth.com/hipaa-notice) as if you were still using the Services.

If you are a Site Visitor, please refer to our [Supplemental State Privacy Notice](https://www.omadahealth.com/state-privacy) for more information on your rights to deletion.

### NOTICE TO RESIDENTS OF CALIFORNIA, COLORADO, CONNECTICUT, UTAH AND VIRGINIA

If you are a resident of California, Colorado, Connecticut, Utah, or Virginia, certain Personal Information we collect from you when accessing or interacting with the Sites is subject to state-specific privacy laws. For these purposes, Personal Information does not include information that is considered PHI under HIPAA or similar state health information privacy laws. Please refer to our [Supplemental State Privacy Notice](https://www.omadahealth.com/state-privacy) for more information on your rights under these laws. 

### HOW DO WE PROTECT CHILDREN’S PERSONAL INFORMATION?

If you are under 18, you may not register or enroll in any Omada Program other than Omada for Joint and Muscle Health, and if you are under 13, you may not register for or enroll in any Omada Program at all. We do not knowingly allow or solicit anyone under these ages to participate independently in any of the Services, and the Services are not directed to children under these ages. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the ages described above. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that a child under the ages above has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we become aware that an individual under the ages above has provided us with Personal Information without verifiable parental consent, we will delete that Personal Information from our files.

### HOW CAN WE CHANGE THIS PRIVACY POLICY?

We may prospectively change or replace any terms of this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason at our discretion. We will post the most recent version of this Privacy Policy on our Sites and in the Apps, and any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective when posted. Use of information we collect is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time the information is used or disclosed. You are responsible for checking this Privacy Policy periodically for changes. If we change or replace any terms of this Privacy Policy in a manner that meaningfully reduces your rights, we will notify you and designate a reasonable time period before the new terms will take effect. By continuing to use or access the Services after any changes come into effect, you agree to be bound by the updated Privacy Policy. If you disagree with any changes, you should stop using the Services.

### HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US WITH QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS?

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or Omada’s privacy practices or if you would like to request to access or correct your Personal Information, please contact our support line at 888-409-8687 or our Privacy Officer, either by email at [privacy@omadahealth.com](mailto:privacy@omadahealth.com) or at the following address:

Omada Health, Inc.

c/o Privacy Officer

500 Sansome St., Suite 200 

San Francisco, CA  94111

We will make every effort to respond to your questions, concerns, and requests within a reasonable time.

Effective Date:  April 1, 2024

1\.  We arrange for certain aspects of the Omada for Joint & Muscle Health Program to be delivered by licensed physical therapists who work as employees or contractors of one or more professional corporations or similar organizations with which we are affiliated, including Physera Physical Therapy Group, P.C. (the “Professional  Entities”).

2\. Physical therapists who supply health care services to Omada for Joint & Muscle Health use a specific, web-based application to provide those services. If you are a physical therapist supplying health care services as part of Omada for Joint & Muscle Health, these Terms do not apply to you in that capacity.

* * *

Política de privacidad
----------------------

Bienvenidos a Omada. Nos tomamos en serio su privacidad y queremos que esté familiarizado con cómo recopilamos, usamos y compartimos su información personal. Lea atentamente esta política de privacidad (la “Política de privacidad”) porque contiene información importante sobre sus derechos legales. 

Esta Política de privacidad forma parte de los [Términos de uso](https://www.omadahealth.com/terms-of-use), que son términos vinculantes entre usted y nosotros. En esta Política de privacidad, “nosotros” y “Omada” se refieren a Omada Health, Inc. y sus afiliadas y subsidiarias (y las Entidades Profesionales descritas en la nota al pie de página a continuación). Cualquier término en mayúscula que no esté definido en esta Política de privacidad tendrá el significado que se le atribuye a esos términos en los Términos de uso. 

Esta Política de privacidad se aplica al acceso y uso que haga de los siguientes servicios, a los que nos referimos en su conjunto como los “Servicios”:

* nuestros programas digitales de atención médica (los “Programas de Omada”).1
* nuestras aplicaciones móviles, incluidas Omada y Omada for Joint & Muscle Health (las “Aplicaciones”);
* los sitios web que operamos (incluidos [go.omadahealth.com](https://go.omadahealth.com/) y  [www.omadahealth.com](https://www.omadahealth.com/) y www.physera.com) (los “Sitios”); y 
* todos los servicios y funciones relacionados que  ofrecemos.

A lo largo de esta Política de privacidad, distinguimos entre personas que utilizan diferentes aspectos de nuestros Servicios con las siguientes condiciones:2

* “Miembros de Omada” se refiere a personas que solicitan, se registran y/o se inscriben en uno o más Programas de Omada mientras interactúan con los Programas de Omada y/o utilizan las Aplicaciones; mientras que
* “Visitantes del sitio” se refiere a personas que visitan los Sitios y otros aspectos de nuestros Servicios sin interactuar con el programa de Omada y/o usar las Aplicaciones como Miembros de Omada.

En esta Política de privacidad, describimos cómo recopilamos, conservamos, usamos, divulgamos y procesamos determinada información sobre usted. Cuando accede a cualquier aspecto de los Servicios o utiliza alguno de ellos, usted acepta esta Política de privacidad y nuestra recopilación, conservación, uso, divulgación y procesamiento de su Información personal, todo como se describe en esta Política de privacidad. 

Si es Miembro de Omada, también reconoce expresamente que ha leído y comprendido nuestro [Aviso de prácticas de privacidad de la HIPAA](https://www.omadahealth.com/hipaa-notice). Nuestro Aviso de prácticas de privacidad de la HIPAA describe cómo podemos usar y divulgar la información médica que recibimos mientras le brindamos atención médica a través de los Programas de Omada, incluso en el proceso de solicitud de los Programas de Omada. Usamos esta información para el tratamiento, el pago o las operaciones de atención médica y para otros fines permitidos o requeridos por las leyes aplicables, incluida la Ley de Responsabilidad y Portabilidad del Seguro Médico de 1996, según sus modificaciones periódicas (“HIPAA”). Para los miembros de Omada, en la medida en que surja algún conflicto entre esta Política de privacidad y el Aviso de prácticas de privacidad de la HIPAA, prevalecerá el Aviso de prácticas de privacidad de la HIPAA.

Además, para los Miembros de Omada y Visitantes del sitio ubicados en California, Colorado, Connecticut, Utah y Virginia, se encuentra disponible información adicional sobre nuestras prácticas de privacidad de conformidad con las leyes de privacidad específicas de cada estado [aquí](https://www.omadahealth.com/state-privacy).

### ¿CUÁL ES EL OBJETIVO DE ESTA POLÍTICA DE PRIVACIDAD?

La protección y el uso de la información personal son partes importantes de nuestro negocio. Esta Política de privacidad explica cómo recopilamos, conservamos, usamos, divulgamos y procesamos su Información personal, lo que incluye, entre otras cosas, cómo recopilamos, almacenamos, evaluamos, modificamos, eliminamos, combinamos, compartimos y transferimos esa información. 

No alquilaremos ni venderemos su Información personal, ni tampoco permitiremos que los socios comerciales que contratamos para prestar nuestros Servicios alquilen o vendan su Información personal. Además, no compartiremos su Información personal con terceros para sus propios fines, excepto cuando usted lo autorice, indique o así lo disponga (como se describe a continuación) y excepto, para los miembros de Omada, donde esas divulgaciones se describen en nuestro [Aviso de prácticas de privacidad de la HIPAA](https://www.omadahealth.com/hipaa-notice) (tales como divulgaciones de información médica protegida a sus otros proveedores de atención médica o a otras entidades que tienen determinadas relaciones con usted según la ley HIPAA). Podemos transferir Información personal en relación con una transferencia de parte de nuestro negocio, pero si lo hacemos, exigiremos que la entidad cesionaria cumpla con los términos y condiciones de esta Política de privacidad.

En algunos casos, puede solicitarnos que compartamos información con empresas no afiliadas. Por ejemplo, puede indicar, disponer o autorizarnos a compartir información, incluida información médica confidencial, con Apple HealthKit o servicios similares de Google, o con otras empresas en línea con las que interactúa. Cuando usted decide indicarnos que compartamos información con empresas no afiliadas, visita sitios web de Proveedores externos o emplee Ofertas de terceros, dichas empresas no estarán vinculadas por ninguna de las cláusulas de nuestros Términos de uso, Política de privacidad o Aviso de prácticas de privacidad de la HIPAA. Estas cláusulas y términos no se aplican a las prácticas de terceros que no controlamos ni a los productos o servicios que brindan. Para obtener más información sobre Ofertas de terceros y Proveedores externos, revise los Términos de uso. Usted es el único responsable de comprender los términos de uso y las políticas de privacidad de esas empresas no afiliadas y cómo utilizan y mantienen su información.

### ¿QUÉ CUBRE ESTA POLÍTICA DE PRIVACIDAD?

Esta Política de privacidad cubre cómo usamos y divulgamos la Información personal que recopilamos, comenzando desde el momento en que accede por primera vez a uno de nuestros Sitios o Aplicaciones y de forma continua a medida que usa o accede a los Sitios, las Aplicaciones y los Programas de Omada u otros aspectos de nuestros Servicios. Como proveedor de atención médica, Omada también se dedica a mantener la privacidad e integridad de la información médica protegida que recibimos de los Miembros de Omada a través de exámenes clínicos en línea o como parte de las solicitudes para acceder a los Programas de Omada o por su participación en ellos, incluida la información médica que recopilamos a través de dispositivos digitales que se utilizan en relación con los Programas de Omada. 

Información personal: en general

En esta Política de privacidad, utilizamos el término "Información personal" para referirnos a la información que recopilamos y que se podría usar para identificarlo o contactarlo, así como cualquier otra información identificable que recopilamos sobre el uso o potencial uso que haga de los Servicios. Entre los ejemplos de información personal se incluyen su nombre y apellido, la información de su perfil personal, su dirección de correo electrónico u otra información de contacto y todos los Envíos de usuario. La información personal que recibimos puede incluir "información personal", tal como ese término se define en las leyes y regulaciones pertinentes, incluidas las leyes vigentes en California, Colorado, Connecticut, Utah y Virginia, donde son aplicadas. Los residentes de estos estados pueden consultar nuestro [Aviso de privacidad estatal complementario](https://www.omadahealth.com/state-privacy) para obtener más información sobre sus derechos.

Información médica protegida

En esta Política de privacidad, utilizamos los términos "Información médica protegida" o "PHI" para referirnos al subconjunto de Información personal que creamos, recibimos, transmitimos o conservamos como parte del registro, la solicitud de un Miembro de Omada para acceder a un Programa de Omada o su participación en este, o que un Miembro de Omada proporciona como parte de nuestros examinadores clínicos en línea, cuando esa información se relaciona con (a) la salud o condición física o mental pasada, presente o futura del Miembro de Omada; (b) la prestación de atención médica al Miembro de Omada; o (c) el pago pasado, presente o futuro del miembro de Omada por esa atención médica. Las leyes federales y estatales le otorgan a los miembros de Omada ciertos derechos con respecto a cualquier acceso a su PHI, así como el uso o la divulgación de esta. Además, nuestro [Aviso de prácticas de privacidad de la HIPAA](https://www.omadahealth.com/hipaa-notice) proporciona información adicional importante sobre cómo podemos usar y divulgar la PHI de los miembros de Omada. 

Su privacidad es importante para nosotros y nos comprometemos a administrar cuidadosamente su Información personal en relación con los Servicios que prestamos. 

### ¿QUÉ INFORMACIÓN PERSONAL RECOPILAMOS?

Recopilamos Información personal suya y de ciertos dispositivos que puede utilizar, como se describe con más detalle a continuación. Para los miembros de Omada, esto incluye información recopilada a través de examinadores clínicos, solicitudes, registros, verificaciones de elegibilidad (incluidas aquella de nuestros Sitios y Aplicaciones, y aquella disponible a través de socios comerciales con los que trabajamos para permitir que las personas verifiquen la cobertura de los Programas de Omada directamente desde ese sitios) y el uso que usted haga de las Aplicaciones y los Programas de Omada. Para los Visitantes del sitio, esto incluye información personal que usted pueda proporcionarnos a través de los Sitios. Tanto para los Miembros de Omada como para los Visitantes del sitio, también recibimos cierta Información personal que se recopila automáticamente, como se describe con más detalle a continuación. También podemos recopilar Información personal a través de fuentes externas (incluidos intermediarios de datos, según se define ese término en las leyes aplicables), como proveedores de servicios de correo electrónico. También recopilamos Información personal en relación con consultas que pueda realizar a través de los Sitios, los Programas de Omada o las Aplicaciones. La recopilación comienza desde el momento en que accede inicialmente a nuestros Servicios.

La información que recopilamos nos permite:

* prestarle los Servicios, 
* administrar las cuentas de los Miembros de Omada,
* enviarle comunicaciones relativas a los servicios que ofrecemos, 
* responder sus consultas, 
* conocer su opinión sobre nuestros Servicios,
* comprender quién utiliza nuestros Servicios y cómo funcionan,
* revisar el comportamiento y la actividad de los Miembros de Omada y de los Visitantes del sitio, 
* personalizar y mejorar nuestros Servicios, 
* llevar a cabo actividades de investigación, 
* gestionar la seguridad de los Servicios, y
* cumplir con cualquier requisito que nos impongan las leyes y regulaciones aplicables.

De vez en cuando, podemos solicitarle información suya a terceros y podemos usar, agregar o actualizar su Información personal con la información obtenida de esos terceros. Por ejemplo, podemos obtener información de contacto de terceros o utilizar información de terceros para confirmar la información de contacto o financiera, para verificar su elegibilidad de cobertura para un Programa Omada o para comprender mejor sus intereses al vincular información demográfica con la información que nos proporcionó. Como proveedor de atención médica, también podemos recibir información sobre los Miembros de Omada de otras entidades del sistema de atención médica, como otros proveedores de atención médica de un Miembro de Omada, la compañía de seguros de un Miembro de Omada o intercambios de datos de salud que permiten a esas entidades compartir Información médica protegida para fines legalmente permitidos. 

En algunos casos, nos proporcionarán Información personal en relación con el uso que hace de los Servicios y, si es Miembro de Omada, esa Información personal puede incluir Información médica protegida. En otros casos, podemos recopilar esta información automáticamente cuando visita o interactúa con los Sitios, las Aplicaciones u otros aspectos de los Servicios. A continuación proporcionamos más detalles sobre los tipos de Información personal que usted proporciona y los tipos de Información personal que recopilamos automáticamente: 

Información personal que usted nos proporciona

Información que usted proporciona directamente. Recibimos y conservamos información que ingresa en nuestros Sitios o mediante una de nuestras Aplicaciones, información recopilada a través de examinadores clínicos, solicitudes, registros, verificaciones de elegibilidad (incluida aquella de nuestros Sitios y Aplicaciones y aquella disponible a través de socios comerciales con los que trabajamos para permitir que las personas verifiquen la cobertura de los Programas de Omada directamente desde ese sitios), información que nos comparte por correo electrónico o teléfono y cualquier otra información que nos proporciona a través de nuestros Servicios. La Información personal que usted proporciona puede incluir su nombre completo, sexo, nombre de usuario y contraseña, información de contacto (por ejemplo, su número de teléfono, su dirección de correo electrónico y la dirección de correo electrónico de sus contactos, direcciones postales residenciales y comerciales), cierta información médica (por ejemplo, peso, condiciones médicas preexistentes, lecturas de glucosa y presión arterial, información sobre su actividad física, sueño, lesiones, niveles de dolor, planes de tratamiento anteriores, mensajes con nuestros equipos de atención y otras actividades), información sobre el seguro médico, Envíos de usuario (como se describe en más detalle en nuestros [Términos de uso](https://www.omadahealth.com/terms-of-use)), tarjeta de crédito y/u otra información de pago (cuando corresponda para los participantes que pagan por su propia participación en los Servicios) y cualquier otra información o datos que usted proporcione al utilizar nuestros Servicios. Si es Miembro de Omada, también puede participar en videoconsultas como parte de un programa de Omada, y reconoce y acepta que podemos grabar estas consultas con fines de capacitación.

Información que proporciona a través de Dispositivos suministrados por Omada. Si es Miembro de Omada, podemos permitirle que nos comparta información en relación con los programas de Omada a través de los equipos digitales que le proporcionamos y que lo ayudan a realizar un seguimiento de los cambios en su salud o estado físico. En muchos casos, el equipo nos proporciona esa información automáticamente y al Programa de Omada correspondiente. Nos referimos a estos dispositivos como “Dispositivos suministrados por Omada”. La mayoría de los Dispositivos suministrados por Omada están preconfigurados para proporcionarnos información y compartirán información sobre los Miembros de Omada y su salud sin solicitarles autorizaciones adicionales. Entre los ejemplos de Información personal que podemos recibir de los Dispositivos suministrados por Omada se incluyen el peso, las lecturas de glucosa en sangre y las lecturas de presión arterial. Puede encontrar más información sobre los Dispositivos suministrados por Omada en nuestros [Términos de uso](https://www.omadahealth.com/terms-of-use). 

Información que indica, dispone o autoriza proporcionar a Fuentes de datos externas. También podemos permitirle que nos comparta información de terceros que han recibido su información porque se suscribió a sus servicios o participa en ellos. Nos referimos a estas fuentes de información como “Fuentes de datos externas”. Para los Miembros de Omada, las Fuentes de datos externas pueden incluir cualquier equipo digital, como monitores de glucosa en sangre o monitores de presión arterial, que ya posee o que luego adquiere por su cuenta y no por parte nuestra (“Dispositivos de salud de terceros”). Podemos recibir Información personal sobre los Miembros de Omada a través de Dispositivos de salud de terceros si el Miembro de Omada ingresa esa información manualmente a través de las Aplicaciones o los Sitios, o permite que el dispositivo nos proporcione información automáticamente. Además de los Dispositivos de salud de terceros, las Fuentes de datos externas también pueden incluir otras fuentes de datos externas a los que indique, disponga o autorice para que nos entreguen información. Para los Miembros de Omada, estas Fuentes de datos externas pueden incluir proveedores externos de atención médica que hayan proporcionado al Miembro de Omada una remisión o una receta y hayan compartido esa información con Omada porque el Miembro de Omada lo indicó, solicitó o autorizó; servicios de salud y bienestar como Apple HealthKit y servicios similares de Google que el Miembro de Omada puede indicar, disponer o autorizar para que nos entreguen esa información; u otras compañías digitales que puedan ayudar a los Miembros de Omada a verificar su cobertura, a disponer o inscribirse en el Programa Omada y que los Miembros de Omada les indiquen, dispongan o autoricen a entregarnos información. Entre los ejemplos de Información personal de miembros de Omada que podemos recibir de Fuentes de datos externas, incluidos los Dispositivos de salud de terceros, se incluyen el peso, las lecturas de glucosa en sangre, las lecturas de presión arterial y la información sobre la actividad física, el sueño y otras actividades. Puede encontrar más información sobre las Fuentes de datos externas, incluidos los Dispositivos de salud de terceros, en nuestros Términos de uso.

Utilizaremos la Información personal que nos proporciona para los fines descritos anteriormente (y para cualquier otro propósito intrínseco a los Servicios que utilice) y para brindarle una experiencia atractiva y personalizada cuando haga uso de los Servicios. Puede optar por no proporcionarnos cierta información, pero si elige esa opción, es posible que no podamos brindarle acceso o permitirle usar muchas de nuestras funciones. 

Información personal compartida con nosotros como su proveedor de atención médica por otras partes

Si es Miembro de Omada, podemos recibir Información personal, incluida Información médica protegida, de otras partes del sistema de atención médica que están legalmente autorizadas a compartir esa información con nosotros como su proveedor de atención médica de conformidad con la ley HIPAA. Por ejemplo, los proveedores externos o planes de salud que le prestaron servicios, como seguros médicos, recetas o remisiones, pueden compartirnos Información personal suya, incluida su Información médica protegida. También podemos obtener Información personal, incluida su Información médica protegida, sobre los Miembros de Omada a partir de intercambios de información médica disponibles para proveedores de atención médica como nosotros para fines, tales como tratamientos y operaciones de atención médica. Este tipo de intercambio se describe con más detalle en nuestro [Aviso de prácticas de privacidad de la HIPAA](https://www.omadahealth.com/hipaa-notice). 

Otra Información personal que obtenemos bajo licencias de terceros

Podemos otorgar licencias o recopilar información, incluidas direcciones de correo electrónico, otra información de contacto y otra Información personal, de terceros, como proveedores de bases de datos de correo electrónico, plataformas de distribución de contenido u organizadores de eventos de la industria. Si le enviamos un correo electrónico utilizando información recopilada de estas fuentes, puede optar por no recibirlos siguiendo las instrucciones allí incluidas para cancelar su suscripción de la misma manera descrita en otras secciones de esta Política de privacidad. Si combinamos o asociamos información de otras fuentes con la Información personal o Información médica protegida que recopilamos a través del Servicio, trataremos la información combinada como Información personal o Información médica protegida en consecuencia, de acuerdo con esta Política de privacidad. 

Información personal recopilada automáticamente

Además de cualquier información que nos proporcione a través de los Servicios o que recibamos de terceros, nosotros y nuestros proveedores de servicios externos podemos utilizar tecnologías variadas que almacenan o recopilan cierta información suya de forma automática (o pasiva) cuando visita o interactuar con los Sitios, las Aplicaciones u otros aspectos de los Servicios (“Información de uso”). Se puede almacenar o acceder a esta Información de uso mediante tecnologías descargadas en su dispositivo cada vez que visite o interactúe con los Servicios. Entre los ejemplos de Información de uso se incluyen: su dirección IP, otros identificadores únicos asignados a su dispositivo que permiten que nuestras computadoras lo reconozcan, detalles de las características y funcionalidad de su dispositivo (por ejemplo, navegador, sistema operativo, información de red móvil), las áreas dentro del Sitio, las Aplicaciones u otros aspectos de los Servicios que visita y de sus actividades, la ubicación de su dispositivo y algunos otros datos relacionados con este. 

En la medida en que asociemos la Información de uso con su Información personal o la Información de uso incluya información identificable, la trataremos como si fuera Información personal. Además, si es Miembro de Omada, en la medida en que asociemos Información de uso con su PHI o recopilemos Información de uso a través de su solicitud para acceder a los programas de Omada o de su participación en ellos, protegeremos esa información como PHI de conformidad con nuestro [Aviso de prácticas de privacidad de la HIPAA](https://www.omadahealth.com/hipaa-notice). 

Información de su navegador o dispositivo

Recibimos y registramos automáticamente la Información de uso de su navegador en los registros de nuestro servidor cada vez que interactúa con el Sitio, las Aplicaciones u otros aspectos de los Servicios. Podemos utilizar esta Información de uso para brindarle atención y asistencia al cliente. También podemos utilizar esta Información de uso para reconocerlo cuando llegue al Sitio desde un enlace externo, por ejemplo desde un enlace que aparece en un sitio externo o en un correo electrónico generado por nosotros. Analizamos este tipo de tecnología con más detalle en “Tecnologías de seguimiento” a continuación. Nuestros Servicios también recopilan Información de uso para determinar con qué frecuencia los Visitantes del sitio y los Miembros de Omada usan partes del Sitio, las Aplicaciones u otros aspectos de los Servicios para así poder mejorarlos y esforzarnos para garantizar que los Servicios atraigan a la mayor cantidad de usuarios y clientes posibles. 

Puede configurar su navegador para que rechace o deshabilite estos métodos de recopilación de datos, pero hacerlo puede cambiar su experiencia con los Sitios, las Aplicaciones u otros aspectos de los Servicios, atenuar ciertos aspectos de la funcionalidad de los Servicios o desactivar ciertas funciones. Por ejemplo, es posible que los Sitios no reconozcan ni respondan a su navegador con las tecnologías de “no seguimiento” empleadas.

Comunicaciones y notificaciones por correo electrónico

Es posible que recibamos una confirmación cuando abra un correo electrónico o una notificación nuestra si su dispositivo admite este tipo de confirmación. Usamos esta confirmación para hacer que nuestros mensajes sean más interesantes y útiles. Si es Miembro de Omada, puede ajustar sus preferencias de correo electrónico y notificaciones en las Aplicaciones y puede cambiar los tipos de notificaciones que recibe en su dispositivo móvil desde configuración. También puede optar por no recibir ningún correo electrónico que enviemos que no esté relacionado con la cuenta de un Miembro de Omada siguiendo las instrucciones incluidas para cancelar su suscripción. Si desea ayuda para cancelar su suscripción a las comunicaciones por correo electrónico, comuníquese con nosotros de cualquiera de las formas descritas al pie de esta Política de privacidad. Tenga en cuenta que, al optar por no recibir más comunicaciones por correo electrónico después de inscribirse en un Programa de Omada, puede limitar los recordatorios del programa así como otros contenidos y componentes valiosos del programa.

Tecnologías de seguimiento

Podemos utilizar varios métodos o tecnologías de seguimiento (“Tecnologías de seguimiento”) para almacenar o recopilar su Información de uso, incluida la información sobre sus visitas o interacciones con nuestros Sitios, Aplicaciones y otros aspectos de los Servicios. Usamos Tecnologías de seguimiento con varios propósitos que creemos necesarios o útiles para mejorar o evaluar el desempeño de los Servicios (por ejemplo, como parte de nuestras prácticas analíticas) o para ofrecerle una función mejorada (por ejemplo, para identificar a los Miembros de Omada cuando inician sesión, para hacer un seguimiento de sus preferencias especificadas o para ayudar a garantizar que la seguridad de las cuentas de los Miembros de Omada no se haya visto comprometida).

Las Tecnologías de seguimiento pueden incluir las siguientes tecnologías y métodos, así como cualquier tecnología y método desarrollados posteriormente para realizar funciones similares:

Cookies. Las cookies son identificadores alfanuméricos que transferimos a su dispositivo a través de su navegador para permitir que nuestros sistemas reconozcan su navegador y nos digan cómo y cuándo visita páginas de nuestro Sitio u otros aspectos de los Servicios. Utilizamos cookies para optimizar las experiencias de los Miembros de Omada y los Visitantes del sitio para comprender cómo interactúan y navegan en nuestro Sitio y con los Servicios. Las cookies habituales se pueden desactivar o eliminar en general ajustando ciertas configuraciones disponibles en la mayoría de los navegadores. En algunos casos (pero no en todos), estas herramientas pueden bloquear esas cookies en el futuro. Cada navegador que utilice deberá configurarse por separado, y diferentes navegadores ofrecen diferentes funciones y opciones en este sentido. Además, es posible que estas herramientas no sean efectivas para ciertos tipos de cookies (por ejemplo, cookies de Adobe Flash o HTML5). Su capacidad para limitar las cookies cuando vuelve a visitar nuestro Sitio o los Servicios está sujeta a la configuración y a las limitaciones de su navegador. Tenga en cuenta que, si desactiva o elimina las cookies en su dispositivo, es probable que algunas partes de nuestros Sitios u otros aspectos de nuestros Servicios no funcionen correctamente.

Scripts integrados. Un script integrado es un código de programación diseñado para recopilar información sobre sus interacciones con los Sitios, las Aplicaciones y otros aspectos de nuestros Servicios, como por ejemplo un enlace en el que puede hacer clic. Los scripts integrados se descargan temporalmente en su dispositivo. Los scripts integrados permanecen activos solo cuando está conectado a los Servicios y luego se desactivan o eliminan.

Web Beacons. Los Servicios también pueden incluir pequeñas imágenes gráficas u otros códigos de programación web llamados “web beacons” (también conocidos como “GIF 1×1” o “imagen GIF transparente”). Cualquier imagen electrónica u otro código de programación web insertado en una página o correo electrónico puede actuar como web beacons, y estos pueden ser invisibles para usted. Los web beacons y las tecnologías similares se pueden utilizar para diversos fines, incluido contar los Visitantes del sitio y los Miembros de Omada que ingresan a los Servicios, contar cuántos correos electrónicos enviados se abrieron, cuántos artículos o enlaces se vieron o monitorear cuántos Visitantes del sitio y Miembros de Omada navegan por los Servicios.

Esta Política de privacidad se refiere únicamente al uso de cookies y otras Tecnologías de seguimiento que hace Omada y no cubre el uso de ninguna Tecnología de seguimiento que hagan anunciantes externos ni ningún otro tercero. Para confirmar cómo un tercero recopila o utiliza su información, consulte el sitio web de ese tercero. Como mencionamos anteriormente, no alquilaremos ni venderemos su Información personal a terceros ni compartiremos su Información personal con terceros para sus propios fines, salvo cuando usted lo disponga, indique o autorice.

### ¿QUIÉN ES EL PROPIETARIO DE LA INFORMACIÓN PERSONAL QUE USTED DIVULGA A LA COMPAÑÍA?

Usted conserva todos los derechos de propiedad o de licencia que posee sobre sus Envíos de usuario (incluida cualquier Información personal y PHI), siempre que cuando utilice los Servicios o revele o indique, disponga o autorice a otros a revelarnos cualquier Envío de usuario, nos otorgue una licencia para esos Envíos de usuario como se describe en nuestros [Términos de uso](https://www.omadahealth.com/terms-of-use), en esta Política de privacidad y, para los Miembros de Omada, en nuestro [Aviso de prácticas de privacidad de la HIPAA](https://www.omadahealth.com/hipaa-notice).

### ¿QUÉ INFORMACIÓN PERSONAL COMPARTIMOS?

Las secciones a continuación describen determinadas circunstancias en las que podemos compartir su Información personal:

Información de los Miembros de Omada que se puede compartir con otros Miembros de Omada

Si, como Miembro de Omada, utiliza o accede a cualquier Programa de Omada que incluya un componente de grupo o comunidad, otros Miembros de Omada tendrán acceso a una variedad de Información personal que usted puede optar por compartir, como se describe a continuación. Estos otros Miembros de Omada pueden ser sus compañeros de trabajo u otros conocidos. Cuando accede a dicho Programa de Omada o lo utiliza, usted autoriza a Omada a revelar a otros miembros de Omada que usted es clínicamente elegible para los Servicios y que participa en aspectos relevantes de los Servicios, lo que puede indicar que cumple con los criterios de inscripción clínica para aspectos relevantes de los Servicios y puede identificarlo como que vive con ciertas enfermedades o condiciones crónicas o está en riesgo de padecerlas. 

Si se inscribe en un Programa de Omada, puede proporcionar en su página de perfil de Miembro de Omada información sobre su salud, síntomas y tratamientos, sus sentimientos sobre su información médica y/o personal, o cualquier otra información personal. También puede cargar imágenes, videos e historias en su página de perfil de Miembro de Omada. Cualquier información que elija incluir cuando crea, completa o actualiza su página de perfil de Miembro de Omada puede estar visible para otros Miembros de Omada, y otros Miembros de Omada pueden publicar comentarios y ver los comentarios publicados en su página de perfil de Miembro de Omada. Para los Miembros de Omada, cierta información resumida sobre su participación, como la cantidad de días que se mantuvo en su último peso o racha de actividad, su porcentaje general de progreso hacia el cumplimiento de sus objetivos y la fecha de su última actividad en el Programa de Omada (“Información resumida”) también puede estar visible para otros Miembros de Omada, pero esta Información resumida no incluirá datos biométricos personales como su peso actual o las lecturas de sus dispositivos. Si es Miembro de Omada, debe proporcionarnos su nombre legal, pero se le permite elegir un apodo y/o una imagen que no sea una fotografía suya para mostrarla en su página de perfil de Miembro de Omada, visible para otros Miembros de Omada. Sin embargo, su Equipo de atención sabrá su nombre legal.

Además, si es Miembro de Omada, en relación con su participación en un Programa de Omada, podemos ubicarlo en un grupo de pares en línea y puede optar por inscribirse en otras comunidades grupales que podamos ofrecerle. El Sitio, las Aplicaciones y otros aspectos de los Servicios pueden incluir la capacidad de interactuar con foros de discusión, salas de chat, páginas de comunidades, páginas de perfil, tableros de anuncios, blogs, mensajería instantánea u otros servicios de mensajería, actividades, encuestas, juegos y otros foros de comunicación en los que publica o pone a disposición información o materiales (“Grupos”). Tenga en cuenta que cualquier información, texto e imágenes que publique o divulgue a través de los Grupos pueden ser vistas por las personas que están actualmente o que estarán en un futuro en esos grupos o comunidades. Para los Miembros de Omada, su ID de Miembro de Omada, su foto de perfil y la información resumida relacionada también pueden estar visibles para otros Miembros de Omada cuando envía mensajes o divulga información a través de estos Grupos en general.

Nos esforzamos mucho por proteger su privacidad, pero recuerde que no podemos controlar cómo otros Miembros de Omada usarán o divulgarán la información que comparte en su página de perfil de Miembro de Omada o que divulga en los Grupos. Lo alentamos a que actúe con discreción y precaución cuando decide divulgar información, incluida su información médica y otra Información personal, en su página de perfil de Miembro de Omada, a través de un Grupo o de otro modo a través de los Servicios. 

### DECLINAMOS EXPRESAMENTE CUALQUIER RESPONSABILIDAD POR EL USO QUE OTROS HAGAN DE CUALQUIER INFORMACIÓN, INCLUYENDO LA INFORMACIÓN PERSONAL, QUE USTED DIVULGUE O SE DIVULGUE A OTROS EN SU NOMBRE EN SU PÁGINA DE PERFIL DE MIEMBRO DE OMADA O A GRUPOS U OTRAS CARACTERÍSTICAS PÚBLICAS DE LOS SERVICIOS, INCLUIDOS LOS FOROS DE DISCUSIÓN, SALAS DE CHAT, SERVICIOS DE MENSAJERÍA U OTROS GRUPOS DESCRITOS ANTERIORMENTE. AL DIVULGAR SU INFORMACIÓN A TRAVÉS DE ESTAS FUNCIONES, USTED RECONOCE Y ACEPTA CUALQUIER RIESGO Y DAÑO QUE SURJA A PARTIR DE LA DIVULGACIÓN DE DICHA INFORMACIÓN.

Comunicaciones en respuesta a los Envíos de usuario

Como parte de los Servicios, recibirá correos electrónicos y otras comunicaciones nuestras relacionadas con sus Envíos de usuario. Usted reconoce y acepta que después de publicar Envíos de usuario podemos enviarle correos electrónicos, mensajes de texto, llamadas telefónicas y otras comunicaciones que determinemos, a nuestro exclusivo criterio, relacionadas con sus Envíos de usuario.

Información compartida con nuestros agentes

Empleamos a otras personas y empresas para realizar tareas en nuestro nombre, y debemos compartir su información con ellas para poder ofrecerle productos y/o servicios. Por ejemplo, puede verificar su elegibilidad o iniciar solicitudes para los Programas de Omada a través de capacidades conectadas que nuestros socios comerciales ofrecen por ser nuestros agentes, y podemos compartir cierta información con esos socios comerciales a medida que habilitan esas verificaciones y servicios relacionados. Al acceder a los Servicios o utilizarlos, usted acepta y autoriza a Omada a revelar su Información personal a nuestro personal y administradores autorizados, incluidos, para los Miembros de Omada, nuestros Equipos de atención y otros agentes autorizados. Le exigimos a cualquier persona o empresa que nos ayude con las tareas que acepte las garantías y limitaciones de privacidad y seguridad adecuadas en el uso que se hace de su Información personal. A menos que tengamos su autorización o consentimiento, no permitimos que estos agentes alquilen o vendan ninguna Información personal suya que reciban de parte nuestra ni que utilicen la Información personal para fines propios. Además, en la medida en que compartamos PHI con estos agentes, solo compartimos con ellos la cantidad de PHI que es mínimamente necesaria para ayudarnos, y nuestros contratos con estas empresas les exigen que cumplan con la HIPAA. 

Información compartida con otras entidades permitidas por la HIPAA, incluidos patrocinadores, administradores externos, proveedores de atención médica externos y sus agentes

Si es Miembro de Omada, podemos, a nuestro exclusivo criterio, compartir, transferir o divulgar parte de su Información personal y PHI a entidades que estén autorizadas a recibir esa información para fines legalmente permitidos de conformidad con la ley HIPAA. 

En determinadas circunstancias y con sujeción a ciertas limitaciones especificadas en la ley HIPAA u otras leyes aplicables, podemos compartir, transferir o divulgar Información personal y PHI a las compañías que pagan por su participación en un Programa de Omada, incluidos sus agentes y administradores externos. 

También podemos compartir, transferir o divulgar Información personal y PHI a otros proveedores de atención médica o entidades que tienen ciertas relaciones con usted de conformidad con la ley HIPAA (incluidos sus agentes), ya sea directamente o a través de intercambios de información médica disponibles para los proveedores de atención médica como nosotros. 

Este tipo de intercambio se describe con más detalle en nuestro [Aviso de prácticas de privacidad de la HIPAA](https://www.omadahealth.com/hipaa-notice). Solo compartimos Información médica protegida de los Miembros de Omada de acuerdo con la ley HIPAA y otros requisitos legales aplicables.

Ofertas promocionales y preferencias de comunicación

De vez en cuando, podemos enviarle comunicaciones sobre promociones. Puede gestionar la recepción de estas comunicaciones por correo electrónico haciendo clic en el enlace “cancelar suscripción” que se encuentra en la parte inferior del correo electrónico. Procesaremos las solicitudes de exclusión voluntaria dentro del tiempo requerido por la ley, aunque tal vez más rápido, pero es posible que siga recibiendo ofertas adicionales a medida que procesamos su solicitud. Si es Miembro de Omada, también puede actualizar sus preferencias de comunicación en su perfil de Miembro de Omada. Tenga en cuenta que los Miembros de Omada no pueden optar por no recibir ciertos correos electrónicos sobre transacciones relacionados con su cuenta (como un correo electrónico que lo notifica sobre una actualización de estos términos). 

Nunca divulgaremos su Información personal a otras empresas para sus propios fines excepto cuando usted lo autorice, indique o así lo instruya y excepto, para los Miembros de Omada, donde esas divulgaciones se describen en nuestro [Aviso de prácticas de privacidad de la HIPAA](https://www.omadahealth.com/hipaa-notice) (tales como divulgaciones de Información médica protegida a sus otros proveedores de atención médica o a otras entidades que tienen determinadas relaciones con usted según la ley HIPAA). En determinadas circunstancias, como cuando los Visitantes del sitio se registran para un seminario web, puede compartir su Información personal con nosotros y con un tercero copatrocinador simultáneamente, que nosotros aclararemos. Como se mencionó anteriormente, usted puede optar por compartir información con empresas no afiliadas, o solicitarnos, indicarnos o autorizarnos a compartir información con empresas no afiliadas, en cuyo caso, dichas empresas no estarán vinculadas por ninguna de las cláusulas de nuestros Términos de uso, nuestra Política de privacidad o nuestro Aviso de prácticas de privacidad de la HIPAA. Usted es el único responsable de comprender los términos de uso y las políticas de privacidad de esas empresas no afiliadas y cómo utilizan y mantienen su información.

Información disponible para los Proveedores de Aplicaciones

Al descargar cualquiera de las Aplicaciones de un Proveedor de Aplicaciones, como Apple App Store o Google Play, tenga en cuenta que el Proveedor de Aplicaciones y sus agentes pueden identificarlo como Miembro de Omada o como otro usuario de nuestros Servicios.

Información compartida con otras empresas que no controlamos 

Para brindarle una experiencia óptima de usuario, nuestros Servicios pueden permitirle comunicarse con empresas externas para obtener servicios o productos relacionados. Por ejemplo, podemos permitir que los Miembros de Omada se comuniquen con proveedores externos de atención médica que puedan proporcionarle referencias para tratamientos o recetas. En otras situaciones, podemos proporcionar servicios o vender productos conjuntamente con empresas afiliadas. Debería poder reconocer cuándo una empresa externa está asociada con sus transacciones. 

Cómo compartir según sus instrucciones. En determinadas circunstancias, puede optar por disponer, indicarnos o autorizarnos a compartir información con estas empresas externas de conformidad con sus propias condiciones de uso y políticas de privacidad. En estas circunstancias, usted es el único responsable de comprender las condiciones de uso y las políticas de privacidad de esas empresas y cómo utilizan y mantienen su información. 

Cómo compartir cuando lo permite la ley. En otras circunstancias, cuando estas empresas externas estén autorizadas a recibir su PHI para fines permitidos de conformidad con la ley HIPAA, podemos compartir, transferir o divulgar parte de su PHI a estas empresas externas, como se describe con más detalle anteriormente en esta Política de privacidad y en nuestro Aviso de prácticas de privacidad de la HIPAA. En estas circunstancias, esas empresas externas serán responsables de usar y proteger su PHI de conformidad con la HIPAA. 

En ningún caso, dichas empresas externas quedarán obligadas por ninguna de las cláusulas de los Términos de uso, la Política de privacidad de Omada o el Aviso de prácticas de privacidad de la HIPAA.

Referencias a familiares, colegas y amigos

De vez en cuando, podemos pedirle o invitarlo a que recomiende nuestros Servicios a familiares, colegas o amigos. Le pedimos que limite sus invitaciones a personas de su círculo íntimo que puedan estar interesadas en nuestros Servicios. En estos casos, es su responsabilidad asegurarse de que estas personas sean efectivamente miembros de su familia o personas con quienes tiene una relación personal (basada en la frecuencia de la comunicación, intereses u opiniones compartidas, etc.). Si referimos a una de estas personas a nuestros Servicios, podemos informarle que usted nos ha sugerido que podría estar interesado en probar nuestros Servicios. Si solicitan que no los contactemos nuevamente, no lo haremos.

Nuestras transferencias comerciales

Nos reservamos el derecho de divulgar y transferir toda la Información personal a un operador de los Sitios o de cualquiera de las Aplicaciones, Programas o bases de datos aplicables, siempre y cuando el operador acepte estar sujeto a los términos y condiciones aplicables de esta Política de privacidad. También nos reservamos el derecho de revelar y transferir toda la Información personal a un cesionario de Omada en relación con una fusión, consolidación, reestructuración o cambio de control, la venta de sustancialmente todas nuestras participaciones y/o activos, u otro tipo de cambio a nivel organización (incluso durante el curso de cualquier proceso de diligencia debida), siempre que la entidad cesionaria acepte estar sujeta a los términos y condiciones de esta Política de privacidad.

Protección de Omada y otros

Podemos divulgar su Información personal cuando creamos de buena fe que divulgar esa información es necesario para cumplir con la ley aplicable o una citación u orden de un tribunal de justicia o autoridad similar con jurisdicción, para hacer cumplir nuestras condiciones de uso y otros acuerdos, o para proteger los derechos, la propiedad o la seguridad de Omada, nuestros Equipos de atención, otros empleados nuestros, Miembros de Omada, Visitantes del sitio u otros. Podemos intercambiar información con otras empresas y organizaciones para detectar, anular o proteger contra el fraude y a los fines de la reducción del riesgo crediticio. Si es necesario y así lo exige la ley, divulgaremos cualquier violación de la seguridad, confidencialidad o integridad de su Información personal, incluidas, entre otras, violaciones de su “Información personal” o “información médica” no cifrada y conservada electrónicamente (como lo definen las leyes aplicables). En la medida en que lo permitan las leyes aplicables, podemos hacer estas divulgaciones por correo electrónico o mediante una publicación visible en su perfil privado en los Servicios lo más rápido posible y sin demoras ilógicas, siempre que esto sea consistente con las necesidades legítimas en lo que respecta a la aplicación de la ley y a cualquier otra medida necesaria para determinar el alcance de la violación y restaurar la integridad razonable del sistema de datos.

Datos anónimos

Como se describe en nuestros [Términos de uso](https://www.omadahealth.com/terms-of-use), podemos no identificar los Envíos de usuario que usted nos comparta, incluida cualquier Información personal, o procesarlos de otro modo para que ya no sean atribuibles a usted sin información adicional (“Datos anínimos”). Podemos utilizar esos Datos anónimos sin restricción alguna de cualquier forma permitida por ley. Por ejemplo, podríamos utilizar Datos anónimos para comprender, evaluar o modificar los Servicios, para generar información estadística sobre los Servicios que compartimos con nuestros clientes y otros terceros que evalúan, analizan, acreditan o investigan los Programas de Omada o para otros fines comerciales que podamos tener. Cuando una ley aplicable requiera que utilicemos un método particular para no identificar datos o hacer que ya no sean atribuibles a usted, lo haremos cumpliendo con esa ley. De lo contrario, podemos utilizar un método que sea apropiado según las circunstancias y que no lo identificará razonablemente. 

### ¿ESTÁ ASEGURADA MI INFORMACIÓN PERSONAL?

Empleamos medidas administrativas, físicas y técnicas estándar según la industria que son diseñadas para salvaguardar y proteger la información bajo nuestro control contra el acceso, uso y divulgación no autorizados. Además, cuando recopilemos, conservemos, usemos, divulguemos y procesemos su Información personal, lo haremos utilizando sistemas y procesos consistentes con los requisitos de privacidad y seguridad de la información de las leyes federales y estatales aplicables, incluida, para los Miembros de Omada, la ley HIPAA.

Su cuenta individual de Miembro de Omada también está protegida por una contraseña para su privacidad y seguridad. Para ayudar a evitar el acceso no autorizado a su cuenta y a su Información personal, le sugerimos que proteja su contraseña de manera adecuada, limite el acceso a sus dispositivos y navegadores y cierre sesión una vez que haya terminado de acceder a su cuenta.

Además, en la medida en que usted sea Miembro de Omada y su dispositivo permita que nuestras Aplicaciones le envíen notificaciones automáticas, podremos enviarle notificaciones automáticas que incluyan Información personal y, en casos limitados, la PHI que no esté cifrada en su dispositivo. De manera similar, en la medida en que sea Miembro de Omada y nos brinde permiso para enviarle mensajes de texto, podremos enviarle mensajes de texto que incluyan Información personal y, en casos limitados, la PHI que no esté cifrada. Dependiendo de la configuración de su dispositivo, las notificaciones automáticas y los mensajes de texto pueden ser vistos por otras personas que encuentren su dispositivo. En la mayoría de los casos, puede optar por no recibir notificaciones automáticas o cambiar la configuración de visibilidad de las notificaciones automáticas y de los mensajes de texto cambiando la configuración de su dispositivo. En la medida en que no cambie esta configuración, usted acepta recibir notificaciones automáticas y mensajes de texto autorizados y ser responsable de la seguridad y confidencialidad de cualquier información que muestren las notificaciones automáticas y los mensajes de texto en sus dispositivos. No somos responsables de la Información personal o de otra información que otros puedan encontrar porque obtienen acceso a sus contraseñas, sus dispositivos, sus cuentas de correo electrónico, sus navegadores o su historial de navegación.

Los Servicios pueden contener enlaces a Ofertas de terceros (como se describe más detalladamente en los [Términos de uso](https://www.omadahealth.com/terms-of-use)). Cuando accede a cualquier Oferta de terceros, lo hace bajo su propio riesgo y comprende y acepta que es el único responsable de leer y comprender los términos de uso y/o políticas de privacidad que aplican a esas Ofertas de terceros. No somos responsables de las políticas y/o prácticas de privacidad de ninguna Oferta de terceros, ni somos responsables de la disponibilidad, rendimiento, fallas técnicas, contenido, exactitud, eficacia, idoneidad, seguridad, legalidad o de cualquier otro aspecto de las Ofertas de terceros.  

Actuamos con cautela cuando se trata de proteger su Información personal. Sin embargo, no podemos garantizar la seguridad o confidencialidad de ningún Sistema o Conexión que utilice para transmitirnos información. Por ejemplo, no podemos garantizar que su correo electrónico, su teléfono móvil o cualquier otro dispositivo personal sean seguros. Además, las líneas de comunicación utilizadas para transmitir correos electrónicos y mensajes de texto no tienen las mismas características de seguridad integradas a nuestros Servicios. Para obtener más información sobre sus sistemas y conexiones, consulte los [Términos de uso](https://www.omadahealth.com/terms-of-use). 

Aunque actuamos con cautela para proteger su Información personal, no podemos garantizar que los delincuentes u otras personas que actúan ilegalmente no tengan éxito en sus esfuerzos por socavar nuestras medidas de seguridad. La entrada, el acceso o el uso no autorizado de nuestros sistemas o ubicaciones, las fallas de hardware o software, las pérdidas y otros factores pueden comprometer la seguridad de su información en cualquier momento. 

Si tiene motivos para creer que sus datos o sus interacciones con nosotros ya no son seguros o si tiene preguntas relacionadas con la privacidad o la seguridad de los datos, puede comunicarse con nosotros de cualquiera de las maneras descritas al final de esta Política de privacidad. 

### ¿A QUÉ INFORMACIÓN PERSONAL PUEDO ACCEDER Y CORREGIR?

Si es Miembro de Omada, puede acceder a determinada información personal que se describe a continuación a través de la Aplicación o a través del Programa de Omada para visualizar y, en determinadas situaciones, actualizar esa información. Esta lista puede cambiar a medida que cambian los Servicios.

* Nombre y apellido
* Información de la cuenta y del perfil del Miembro de Omada (por ejemplo, apodo e imagen)
* Dirección de correo electrónico
* Dirección de correo postal
* Número de teléfono
* Nombre de usuario y contraseña
* Preferencias de comunicación (por ejemplo, correo electrónico y notificaciones automáticas)
* Datos relacionados con su peso, actividad, seguimiento de alimentos, mediciones de glucosa en sangre, mediciones de presión arterial u objetivos de salud (cuando corresponda a los Programas de Omada en los que participa).

Omada puede optar por no aceptar algún cambio a cierta información clínica si hacerlo genera un registro clínicamente inexacto. Para obtener más información sobre el derecho a corregir o modificar su PHI, consulte nuestro [Aviso de prácticas de privacidad de la HIPAA](https://www.omadahealth.com/hipaa-notice).

Si es Miembro de Omada, también tiene derecho a recibir una copia de su PHI como se describe en nuestro Aviso de prácticas de privacidad de la HIPAA. Si es un Visitante del sitio pero no un Miembro de Omada, puede acceder a determinada Información personal comunicándose con nosotros de cualquiera de las formas descritas a continuación al final de esta Política de privacidad o según lo requiera la ley aplicable, incluso como se describe en el [Aviso de privacidad estatal complementario](https://www.omadahealth.com/state-privacy). 

Para ayudarnos a conservar su información y garantizar que sea precisa y actualizada, actualice su información si han surgido cambios o infórmenos de inmediato de cualquiera de las maneras descritas al final de esta Política de privacidad para que podamos hacer los cambios adecuados. Cuando actualiza la información, a menudo conservamos una copia de la información no revisada en nuestros registros.

### ¿QUÉ DERECHOS Y OPCIONES TENGO CON RESPECTO A MI INFORMACIÓN PERSONAL?

Elegir no revelar

Puede optar por no revelarnos información, aunque esa información pueda ser necesaria para aprovechar ciertas funciones de los Servicios. 

Solicitar información

También tiene derecho a solicitarnos cierta información, específicamente:

* una copia de la Información personal que recopilamos,
* una descripción de secciones específicas de su Información personal que recopilamos,
* una descripción de las categorías de su Información personal que recopilamos (que puede encontrar en esta Política de privacidad),
* una descripción de las fuentes de Información personal que recopilamos (que puede encontrar en esta Política de privacidad), y 
* una descripción de los fines para los cuales recopilamos su Información personal (que puede encontrar en esta Política de privacidad y, para los Miembros de Omada, en nuestro Aviso de prácticas de privacidad de la HIPAA). 

Los Miembros de Omada también tienen derechos con respecto a nuestro acceso a su Información médica protegida y el uso que hacemos de ella, los cuales se describen con más detalle en nuestro [Aviso de prácticas de privacidad de la HIPAA](https://www.omadahealth.com/hipaa-notice).

También tiene derecho a solicitar información sobre cualquier Información personal que podamos vender o compartir con terceros para sus propios fines. Para su conveniencia y para evitar que nos tenga que solicitar esta información, hemos confirmado en esta Política de privacidad que no alquilaremos ni venderemos su Información Personal. Además, no compartiremos su información personal con terceros para sus propios fines, excepto cuando obtengamos su permiso para hacerlo (como se describe arriba) y excepto, para los Miembros de Omada, cuando esas divulgaciones se describen en nuestro [Aviso de prácticas de privacidad de la HIPAA](https://www.omadahealth.com/hipaa-notice) (tales como divulgaciones de Información médica protegida a sus otros proveedores de atención médica o a otras entidades que tienen determinadas relaciones con usted de conformidad con la ley HIPAA).   

Para solicitarnos información u obtener información adicional e instrucciones para ejercer sus derechos a obtener información, comuníquese con nosotros de cualquiera de las maneras descritas al final de esta Política de privacidad.

Cómo cancelar su suscripción para dejar de recibir comunicaciones

Puede cancelar su suscripción para dejar de recibir nuestras comunicaciones, pero tenga en cuenta que, si es Miembro de Omada, al optar por no recibir más comunicaciones, puede limitar los recordatorios del programa y otros contenidos y componentes valiosos de este. Además, incluso si no desea recibir avisos legales de nuestra parte, como esta Política de privacidad, esos avisos legales seguirán rigiendo su uso de los Servicios y usted es responsable de revisarlos para detectar cambios. Cuando recibe un correo electrónico nuestro, puede optar por dejar de recibirlos siguiendo las instrucciones incluidas para cancelar la suscripción. Además, si es Miembro de Omada, puede ajustar sus preferencias de correo electrónico en las Aplicaciones. Si desea recibir ayuda para cancelar la suscripción a las comunicaciones por correo electrónico o si no desea recibir más correos, llamadas telefónicas o mensajes de texto nuestros, puede indicar esta preferencia comunicándose con nosotros de cualquiera de las maneras descritas al final de esta Política de privacidad. Procesaremos su solicitud dentro de un tiempo razonable, pero tenga en cuenta que puede recibir correos electrónicos adicionales a medida que procesamos su solicitud.

Eliminar su cuenta y/o eliminar Información personal

Como proveedor de atención médica, la ley nos exige conservar la Información personal, incluida cualquier PHI, que recibimos de los Miembros de Omada como un registro comercial. Como resultado, no podemos eliminar los Envíos de usuario u otra Información personal de los Miembros de Omada de nuestros registros. Ciertas funciones requeridas por Apple App Store o Google Play pueden exigirnos que incluyamos un proceso para solicitar la eliminación de la cuenta. Si bien podemos ayudarlo a cerrar su cuenta y dejar de compartir Información personal con nosotros, nuestras obligaciones de cumplimiento normativo como proveedor de atención médica requerirán que conservemos la Información personal durante el tiempo que la ley lo exija. Sin embargo, incluso si usted es Miembro de Omada y deja de usar nuestros Servicios por cualquier motivo (incluido el cierre de su cuenta), protegeremos cualquier Envío de usuario y otra Información personal que mantengamos de acuerdo con nuestros [Términos de uso](https://www.omadahealth.com/terms-of-use), con esta Política de privacidad y nuestro [Aviso de prácticas de privacidad de la HIPAA](https://www.omadahealth.com/hipaa-notice) como si todavía estuviera usando los Servicios.

Si es un Visitante del sitio, consulte nuestro [Aviso de privacidad estatal complementario](https://www.omadahealth.com/state-privacy) para obtener más información sobre sus derechos de eliminación.

### AVISO A LOS RESIDENTES DE CALIFORNIA, COLORADO, CONNECTICUT, UTAH Y VIRGINIA

Si es residente de California, Colorado, Connecticut, Utah o Virginia, cierta Información personal que recopilamos cuando accede a los Sitios o interactúa con ellos está sujeta a las leyes de privacidad específicas de cada estado. Para estos fines, la Información personal no incluye información que se considere PHI de conformidad con la ley HIPAA o de las leyes estatales similares de privacidad de información médica. Consulte nuestro [Aviso de privacidad estatal complementario](https://www.omadahealth.com/state-privacy) para obtener más información sobre sus derechos de conformidad con estas leyes. 

### ¿CÓMO PROTEGEMOS LA INFORMACIÓN PERSONAL DE LOS NIÑOS?

Si es menor de 18 años, no puede registrarse ni inscribirse en ningún Programa de Omada for Joint and Muscle Health, y si es menor de 13 años, no puede registrarse ni inscribirse en ningún Programa de Omada en absoluto. No permitimos ni solicitamos intencionadamente a ninguna persona menor de estas edades a participar de forma independiente en ninguno de los Servicios, y los Servicios no están dirigidos a niños menores de estas edades. No recopilamos intencionalmente Información personal de niños menores de las edades descritas anteriormente. Si un padre o tutor se entera de que un niño menor de las edades mencionadas nos ha proporcionado Información personal, le solicitamos que se comunique con nosotros. Si nos damos cuenta de que una persona menor de las edades mencionadas anteriormente nos proporcionó Información personal sin el consentimiento verificable de los padres, eliminaremos esa Información personal de nuestros archivos.

### ¿CÓMO PODEMOS CAMBIAR ESTA POLÍTICA DE PRIVACIDAD?

Podemos cambiar o reemplazar cualquier término de esta Política de privacidad, en cualquier momento y por cualquier motivo, a nuestra discreción. Publicaremos la versión más reciente de esta Política de Privacidad en nuestros Sitios y Aplicaciones, y cualquier cambio a esta Política de privacidad entrará en vigencia cuando se publique. El uso de la información que recopilamos está sujeto a la Política de privacidad vigente al momento de su uso o divulgación. Usted es responsable de verificar esta Política de privacidad periódicamente para detectar cambios. Si cambiamos o reemplazamos cualquiera de los términos de esta Política de privacidad de una manera que reduzca significativamente sus derechos, se lo notificaremos y designaremos un período de tiempo razonable antes de que los nuevos términos entren en vigencia. Al continuar usando o accediendo a los Servicios después de que cualquier cambio entre en vigencia, usted acepta estar sujeto a la Política de privacidad actualizada. Si no está de acuerdo con algún cambio, le sugerimos que deje de utilizar los Servicios.

### ¿CÓMO PUEDE CONTACTARNOS POR PREGUNTAS O INQUIETUDES?

Si tiene alguna pregunta o inquietud con respecto a esta Política de privacidad o a las prácticas de privacidad de Omada o si desea solicitar acceso o corregir su Información personal, comuníquese con nuestra línea de asistencia al 888-409-8687 o con nuestro administrador de privacidad, ya sea por correo electrónico a [privacy@omadahealth.com](mailto:privacy@omadahealth.com) o a la siguiente dirección:

Omada Health, Inc.

c/o Administrador de privacidad

500 Sansome St., Suite 200 

San Francisco, CA 94111

Haremos todo lo posible para responder a sus preguntas, inquietudes y solicitudes dentro de un tiempo razonable.

Fecha de vigencia: 1 de abril de 2024

1\. Nos encargamos de que ciertos aspectos del Programa de Omada for Joint & Muscle Health sean impartidos por fisioterapeutas licenciados que trabajan como empleados o contratistas de una o más corporaciones profesionales u organizaciones similares con las que estamos afiliados, incluyendo Physera Physical Therapy Group, P.C. (las “Entidades Profesionales”).

2\. Los fisioterapeutas que brindan servicios de atención médica a Omada for Joint & Muscle Health utilizan una aplicación web específica para brindar esos servicios. Si usted es un fisioterapeuta que brinda servicios de atención médica como parte de Omada for Joint & Muscle Health, estos Términos no le serán de aplicación en calidad de tal.

Effective Date: April 1, 2024

© 2024 Omada Health Inc. All Rights Reserved.

Omada Health, Inc. works in partnership with Physera Physical Therapy Group, PC and other contracted partners to be your Omada care team and deliver certain clinical services as part of the Omada programs.
